<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AbnormalityCardsRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Malkuth">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ScorchedGirl_Walk">
      <Abnormality>Scorched Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เสียงเท้าก้าว</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
เมื่อHPของบรรณารักษ์นั้นเป็น20%หรือต่ำกว่า หากโจมตีศัตรูใด ทำดาเมจเป็น30%ของHP สูงสุดของศัตรู(แรงสุด36) และติด 1-3 เผาไหม้แก่ศัตรู จากนั้นก็ตาย</AbilityDesc>      
      <FlaborText>ฉันมาแกแล้ว แกผู้ซึ่งจะต้องมอดไหม้ไปพร้อมกันกับฉัน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">If I must perish, then join me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It’s just too sad to die alone… You know this feeling well, don’t you?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Wait for me. I am coming to you, who will be reduced to ash…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Step by step… Burn into pitch black char.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Is there anything I can do, me, a scorched dark child?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ScorchedGirl_Atk">
      <Abnormality>Scorched Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เถ้าถ่าน</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อถูกโจมตี ติด 1-3 เผาไหม้แก่ผู้โจมตี และคุณมีโอกาส 40% ได้รับบัฟ 'เต๋าโจมตีทุกลูกติด 1 เผาไหม้ เมื่อโจมตี' ในฉากหน้า (บัฟไม่ซ้อนทับ)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“ร่างสีเถ้าถ่านนั้นสื่อถึงความหวังที่แตกสลายของเด็กน้อย ส่วนไฟที่เผาไหม้สื่อถึงความต้องการที่จะเป็นที่รัก”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">To burn all things that are bright to ashes…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I know very well that my scorched body can’t ever return to normal.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s scary to turn to ashes… But I don’t want this fire to go out.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I can feel happiness through the candlelight. And warmth…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Maybe I’ll freely soar through the sky as ash one day.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ScorchedGirl_Ashes">
      <Abnormality>Scorched Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ไฟไม้ขีด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Combat Page 2 อันที่ใช้หลังเลือกAbnormality pageนี้ จะได้รับสถานะ 'ไฟไม้ขีด'(ไม่รวมเพจประเภท[เมื่อใช้เพจ]) เมื่อใดที่บรรณารักษ์ใช้เพจดังกล่าว จะได้รับ 1 'เศษเถ้า'
เพจที่มีสถานะ'ไฟไม้ขีด'จะแข็งแกร่งขึ้นตามจำนวนเศษเถ้าที่มีอยู่ ทว่าหากมีเศษเถ้า4อันหรือมากกว่า เมื่อใช้เพจ'ไฟไม้ขีด' มีโอกาส 25%ที่จะทำดาเมจแก่ผู้ใช้ด้วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“ก็นะ เธอดูเหมือนกับระเบิดเวลาที่เดินอยู่ ไม่มีใครรู้ว่าเธออารมณ์ดีอยู่หรือไม่”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Step by step… Burn into pitch black char.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">What will show up when I light the next match?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You’ll leave me when the light of the last match goes out, won’t you?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">This light is my only hope…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">When a shooting star falls from the sky, it means someone went to heaven. I wonder whose star that is…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HappyTeddyBear_Hug">
      <Abnormality>Happy Teddy Bear</Abnormality>
      <CardName>วันวานน่าหวนคิดถึง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อชนะการปะทะ มีโอกาส20% ทำดาเมจStaggerเพิ่มเติมเท่าค่าเต๋าของคุณ
หากปะทะกับเป้าหมายเดิมหลายครั้ง โอกาสดังกล่าวจะเพิ่มขึ้น</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ตุ๊กตาหมีนั้นกอดผู้คนอย่างเหนียวแน่น เจ้าหมีชอบการกอด แต่มีบางอย่างแปลกๆ</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Give me a tight hug, will you? It’ll soothe your mind.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Everyone loves hugs. Don’t you agree?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Come over here and feel this fuzzy and warm feeling.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">It’s okay. Don’t be afraid. All I do, is wrap you up in my arms.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">You’re tired, aren’t you? Come take a rest in my embrace.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HappyTeddyBear_Memory">
      <Abnormality>Happy Teddy Bear</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความทรงจำแสนสุข</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Combat Pageที่มีคอสเยอะที่สุดจะถูกเลือก(ยกเว้นเพจประเภท[เมื่อใช้เพจ]) เมื่อใช้เพจดังกล่าวหรือเพจที่มีชื่อเดียวกัน จะลดคอสของเพจชื่อนั้นทั้งหมดของตัวละครไป 1 </AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>แต่ว่านะ ตุ๊กตาหมีจะไม่อยากห่างจากเจ้าของของมันแม้แต่นิดเดียว</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Why are you trying to leave me? We were such good friends…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t leave me. You’ll change your mind when I hug you just once more.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s too sad to say goodbye twice…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Why do you have to leave me and promise to meet again?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Have you come to dislike me because I hugged you too tight?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HappyTeddyBear_Lonely">
      <Abnormality>Happy Teddy Bear</Abnormality>
      <CardName>แสดงความรักใคร่</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าทุกลูกได้รับ 1-2 พลัง ในการปะทะ
เต๋าทุกลูกเสีย 1-2 พลัง ในการโจมตีข้างเดียว</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ความทรงจำของมันเริ่มต้นที่กอดอันแสนอบอุ่น</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m so happy that you’re playing with me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You’re a kind one, aren’t you? Let’s do it again, okay?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You were so eager to play with me. I’m touched…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Come over here and feel this fuzzy and warm feeling of love with my hug.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Don’t worry. It’s nothing scary. All I do is wrap you up in my arms.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="FairyCarnival_Care">
      <Abnormality>Fairy Festival</Abnormality>
      <CardName>การดูแลของเหล่าภูต</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
จากนี้ 3ฉาก ฟื้นฟู15%ของMax HP(สูงสุด 18) เมื่อจบฉาก
หากบรรณารักษ์ถูกโจมตี3ครั้ง ขณะที่ความสามารถทำงานอยู่ เสีย25%ของHPปัจจุบันทันที(สูงสุด 30) และหยุดความสามารถนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เหล่าภูตนั้นปกป้องพนักงานของเรา ทุกอย่างจะสงบสุขตราบได้ที่อยู่ภายใต้การดูแลของเหล่าภูต</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Don’t worry, now! We’ll take good care of you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t be alarmed. We’re here to protect you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Fairies are sacred beings, you know. Have some confidence.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You’re a good-hearted lover of nature, you deserve our care.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">You’re the special one. The others should reflect on themselves.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="FairyCarnival_Gluttony">
      <Abnormality>Fairy Festival</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความตะกละ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีเป้าหมายที่เคยถูกโจมตีมาก่อนในฉากเดียวกัน หากโจมตีสำเร็จ ทำดาเมจเพิ่มเติม 1-3 หน่วย และคุณฟื้นฟู 2-5 HP</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เหล่าภูตมันก็เป็นเพียงสัตว์กินเนื้อ การ'ปกป้อง'ที่มันทำก็เป็นเพียงสูตรในการคงเนื้อให้ยังสดอยู่</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The reason we’re staying by your side? Of course it’s to protect you!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Enjoy the fairies’ care to your heart’s content.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">A good person like you shouldn’t die at the hands of anyone else.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">We won’t harm you, as long as you don’t do anything evil.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Are you doubting us? That’s a wicked thought you have…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="FairyCarnival_QueenAtk">
      <Abnormality>Fairy Festival</Abnormality>
      <CardName>นักล่า</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
พันธมิตรทุกคนยกเว้นบรรณรักษ์ที่เลือกจะเสีย 10 HP
นำHPที่เสียของทุกคนมาฟื้นฟูHPของยรรณารักษ์ดังกล่าว และได้รับ 3 กำลัง กับ 3 ว่องไว ในฉากนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ส่วนหน้าและท้องเขาถูกกระชาก ดวงตาและอวัยวะถูกทำร้ายหรือถูกกินโดยบางอย่าง ขณะเดียวกัน ที่ปากของเหล่าภูตนั้นมีกลิ่นเลือดตลบอบอวนไปหมด</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">My fairies are dwindling in numbers… But it can’t be helped.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Scarred and rotten meat isn’t tasty!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I need something fresh. Spoiled meat isn’t nutritious.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I must eat it before it spoils, hm?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Scarred and rotten meat isn’t tasty.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenBee_Funga">
      <Abnormality>Queen Bee</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ละออง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อถูกโจมตี ผู้โจมตีติด 1-3 เผาไหม้ และ 1-3 เลือดไหล ในฉากหน้า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เป็นที่ยืนยันแล้วว่าละอองเหล่านี้แบกเอาไข่ที่จะไปฝักในตัวเหยื่อได้</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Even if a drone dies, I can always make more to fill their role.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">To bring my kingdom to greatness… I need more bees…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Do you know where all my drones have gone to?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Look at the great blue sky while you can.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenBee_Bee">
      <Abnormality>Queen Bee</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ผึ้งงาน</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ศัตรูที่ทำดาเมจแก่บรรณารักษ์ที่เลือก มากที่สุด จะถูกเล็ง พันธมิตรคนอื่นจะโจมตีศัตรูที่ถูกเล็งรุนแรงขึ้น 2-4 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>พวกมันแสดงพฤติกรรมแค่2แบบเท่านั้น คือการนำสารอาหารไปให้ราชินี และการแพร่พันธุ์</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">My bees. It is time to move.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Your wings, legs, jaw… Put every part of your body to work. Lest they pillage our honey.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Make haste, my minions. We cannot waste a minute.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Who will remember the bees that have died for the kingdom…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenBee_Loyalty">
      <Abnormality>Queen Bee</Abnormality>
      <CardName>จงรักภักดี</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก พันธมิตรทุกคนได้รับ กำลัง ขึ้นอยู่กับดาเมจที่บรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือกได้รับในฉากก่อนหน้า
(1 กำลัง ต่อ ดาเมจ 5 หน่วย)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ความจงรักของผึ้งนั้นเป็นสัญชาตญาณโดยกำเนิด หากเราค้นพบการดึงมันออกมาใช้ได้ หลายอย่างจะไม่เหมือนเดิม</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Hurry and supply me with more honey.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I am the kingdom, and the kingdom is I. Loyalty to me is loyalty to your kingdom.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Even if your wings are torn, you should give your everything to serve as long as your legs are working.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">“Giving one’s life” is an empty vow. What I want from you is to survive and continue to protect me.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SnowWhite_Vine">
      <Abnormality>Snow White’s Apple</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เถาวัลย์</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ตลอดทั้งองก์จากนี้ เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ติด 6 พันธนา แก่ศัตรู 1 ตัวแบบสุ่ม
เต๋าแบบแทงได้รับบวก 1-2 พลังเมื่อโจมตีศัตรูดังกล่าว</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>วันหนึ่ง มันได้งอกกิ่งก้านสาขาออกมา ทั้งที่กิ้งและใบนั้นเหี่ยวเชาไปแล้ว มันก็ยังคงงอกต่อไป</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The apple was alone for such a long time. Only rotting corpses kept its side…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The vines were withered and dry, but they always embraced the apple.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">How I wish to bind the two feet of the person who was blessed by my existence and then left.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Those who bit into the apple fell asleep like the princess did, except they couldn’t ever wake up.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SnowWhite_Thorn">
      <Abnormality>Snow White’s Apple</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กำแพงหนาม</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อถูกโจมตี ผู้โจมตีได้รับดาเมจ 2-8 หน่วย และ 1-3 พันธนา
หากผู้โจมตีได้รับ 3 พันธนาไปในครั้งเดียว คุณได้ฟื้นฟูHP เท่ากับดาเมจที่ได้รับพร้อมความสามารถนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>แอปเปิ้ลที่ร่วงลงจากมือของสโนว์ ไวท์ ซึ่งถูกเธอกัดไปเพียงครั้ง ไม่อาจมีสุขได้ เจ้าแอปเปิ้ลเต็มไปด้วยความเหงาและความเกลียดชั้งต่อเจ้าหญิงผู้ชั่วร้าย รอวันที่มันจะเน่าเสียและกับสู่ธรณี</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">A pretty apple, abandoned in a forlorn place. Oh, pretty apple…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The apple couldn’t return to the earth, and only rotting impurities were around it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The apple that was dropped on the dirt floor couldn’t be happy.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Thorned vines grew from the wounded heart.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SnowWhite_malice">
      <Abnormality>Snow White’s Apple</Abnormality>
      <CardName>อาฆาต</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ศัตรูทุกคนรับดาเมจ โดยแปรผันไปตามจำนวนของHPที่บรรณารักษ์ที่เลือก เหลืออยู่(น้อยสุด 5 มากสุด 30; เลือดน้อยต่อยนัก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ความอาฆายโดยกำเนิด นำพาสรรพชีวิตให้แตกสลาย ในคราที่มันได้เบ่งบาน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">My existence was born from wrath and a curse, yet I served as a blessing to someone else.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The lifeless vines continued to grow.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It grew, swallowing dreadful thoughts of revenge, anger at itself… and loneliness.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Yesod">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Tie">
      <Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
      <CardName>โทสะโซ่พันธนา</CardName>
		<AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าทุบได้รับพลัง 1-3 หน่อย ความเร็วถูกตั้งให้เป็น 1</AbilityDesc>
		<FlaborText>เขากำลังใส่เสื้อกักตัว ก็ยังไม่ต่างจากการปล่อยไว้เฉยๆ จะโซ่สักกี่เส้นก็ไม่อาจรั้งเขาไว้จากการสร้างความรุนแรงได้เลย</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Even if my body is tied… I’ll be as free as any man.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Release me… Why do I have to be bound!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Don’t look at me with those eyes. You’re the most pitiful ones here…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You’re not going to keep me shackled with this!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I may be a mess now, but you’ll have to fear me all the same.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Metal">
      <Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เสียงก้องจากโลหะ</CardName>
		<AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีทุบสำเร็จ ติด 1 พันธนา และ 1 อัมพาตฉากหน้า (ยกเว้นการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
		<FlaborText>“หัวฉัน...กลายเป็นเหล็ก...พับสมองของฉัน ให้เรียบแบน...”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">My head is ringing. I can hear the sound of metal, clear and loud…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It feels as if my head is turning to cold steel.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Is my head actually turning into metal?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">When I bash my head onto a wall, it makes a refreshing sound.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">If my head turns into steel, all the wrinkles in my brain will be gone.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Violence">
      <Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความรุนแรง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ลดค่าต่ำสุดของเต๋าทุกลูกไป 1 และเพิ่มค่าสูงสุดไป 3</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“ที่น่าเวทนาก็คือคนอย่างแก ดันมาตายโดยน้ำมือคนอยากฉัน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Don’t think that you’ve won by chaining me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">………</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Ends… Begins. Ends again, begins once more…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">When I bash my head onto a wall, it makes a refreshing sound.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Rest">
      <Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ชาร์จพลัง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หากเริ่มฉากแล้วบรรณารักษ์มีแสงเต็ม ได้รับ 1-2 ว่องไว และทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 2-7 หน่วยเมื่อโจมตีในฉากนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ยังไงก็ตาม แขนขาของมันกับเป็นอุปกรณ์แหลมคม แทนที่จะเป็นของทำความสะอาด</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Beepboop… Beep… Out of battery…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Please… recharge… to a nearby socket…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Please shut down… The helper-bot will switch off soon…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Switching to charge mode. You cannot give orders in this mode.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Pattern">
      <Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ตรวจรับรูปแบบการทำงานประเภททำซ้ำ</CardName>
		<AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อชนะการปะทะครบสามครั้ง ฟื้นฟู 1 แสง และได้รับ 1-2 ว่องไว ฉากหน้าAfter every three clash wins, restore 1 Light and gain 1-2 Haste next Scene.</AbilityDesc>
		<FlaborText>ในวันที่ฉันถูกส่งไปบ้านใหม่เป็นครั้งแรก ฉันจึงให้ของขวัญที่เขาอยากได้นักได้หนา</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">When I’m done cleaning, people would always praise me!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">They’re giving me orders with a loud voice. That means I’m doing a good job.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Beepboop~ Piii! Pattern data accumulated.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">People love to shout when they compliment me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">The helper-bot has excellent learning capabilities.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Clean">
      <Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ปัดกวาด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าโจมตีได้รับพลังมากขึ้นกับศัตรูที่ความเร็วน้อยกว่า (+1พลังทุกๆความต่าง สูงสุด 3)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>พวกมันจะมองอารมณ์ที่ไม่ดีของคน แปลได้ว่ารอบๆข้างนั้นสกปรก แล้วทำการเข้าสู่โหมดทำความสะอาด</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The helper-bot can help you with any household chores!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">What kind of task do you want me to do? I can help with anything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Contamination scan complete. Initiating cleaning protocol.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Beebeebeep~ Beep. Contamination spotted! Proceeding with trash disposal protocol.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I will help you with my wide selection of tools.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
	  <AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Music">
		  <Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
		  <CardName>บทเพลง</CardName>
		  <AbilityDesc>[ตัวละครทั้งหมด]
ตัวละครทุกตัวทำดาเมจ +4-8 หน่วยในการรับแขกครั้งนี้ และได้รับดาเมจStagger +4-8 เมื่อถูกโจมตี
เมื่อพันธมิตรฆ่าศัตรูได้ พวกเขาฟื้นฟู 15 HP และ Stagger Resist</AbilityDesc>
		  <FlaborText>ไม่มีเพลงไหนจะเทียบติด กับเพลงในตอนที่มันนั้นกำลังกิมมนุษย์</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Nothing makes as fascinating music as a human can.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t you want to hear a beautiful song? You already know how.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Don’t you worry. I’m sure that one wants to be a fine instrument, too.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">People all carry musical talent in them.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Those who are fortitudinous, come to me. Join me.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
	  </AbnormalityCard>
    
	  <AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Rhythm">
		  <Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
		  <CardName>ทำนอง</CardName>
		  <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ตลอดการต่อสู้นี้ ได้รับ 1 ทำนองเมื่อเริ่มฉาก เมื่อใดก็ตามที่ตัวละครที่มีทำนองนั้นโจมตีสำเร็จ มีโอกาส 25% ที่ตัวละครสุ่มหนึ่งคน ได้รับ 1 ทำนอง ในฉากหน้า.
(ทำนอง: ได้รับ 1 กำลัง, รับดาเมจStaggerมากขึ้น หายไปเมื่อเข้าฉากใหม่)</AbilityDesc>
		  <FlaborText>มันกำลังสรรสร้างทวงทำนอง</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Everyone wants to hear my song again.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Various sounds join together to create music.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">They’re all volunteering to be instruments…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">If everyone threw their bodies into me, it’ll certainly create an even sweeter melody.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">You won’t want to hear any other music anymore.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
	  </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Atk">
      <Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เสพติดในเสียงดนตรี</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าโจมตีบวก 1-3 พลัง
เต๋าป้องกันประเภทตั้งรับจะทอยได้ 1 เท่านั้น</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ยังไงซะ ศิลปะคือของขวัญจากปีศาจ เกิดจากความเศร้าและทรมาณ มันไม่หยุดแสดงจนกว่าร่างจะแหลกละเอียดเป็นผง</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">All other music is nothing more than noise to me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Make me move… Light my path with the songs!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Hahaha… Ha… What will I do? What can I do? Haha…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Eternal happiness would be mine if this tune lasted forever…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Yes! This is it… Behold this powerful melody!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_White">
      <Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>พักผ่อนชั่วกาล</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีศัตรูที่HPปัจจุบันน้อยที่สุด ทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 2-7 หน่วย และ ดาเมจStagger มากขึ้น 2-5 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ผู้คนเชื่อว่าเมื่อตายแล้ว พวกเขาจะกลายเป็นสิ่งมีชีวิตอันสวยงามพร้อมกับปีกสีขาว เป็นเรื่องราวที่น่าขัน ไร้สาระจริงๆ</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">An eternal rest… May you rest in peace.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">They believed that they would become beautiful beings with small wings when they died.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I’ll help liberate you from tormenting yourselves.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">They must have returned home, having earned what they wanted and being full of hope.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Death may seem fearsome, it doesn’t compare to the terror of reality. It’ll feel liberating, rather.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_Fly">
      <Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>อาวรณ์</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 2-4 หน่วย กับศัตรูที่กำลังติดสถานะทางลบอยู่
หากบรรณารักษ์ติดสถานะทางลบเมื่อเริ่มฉาก ได้รับ 1-2 กำลัง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>พวกเขาบอกว่า ผู้อาวรณ์ซึ่งแบกสัมภาระอันใหญ่ไว้ที่หลังของเขานั้น กำลังกลับมาเพื่อกอบกู้พวกเรา</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">For you poor souls who cannot stop grieving… I offer my condolences.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Grief for the dead, and early lament for the living.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Frivolous forms of sadness such as tears will only wet the wings.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Not a sliver of impurity is allowed for the mind of those who mourn, for it must remain reverent and solemn.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Not a single proper flower blooms to honor the butterflies.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_Casket">
      <Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>โลงศพ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีศัตรูที่HPเป็น50%หรือต่ำกว่า ผนึกลูกเต๋าความเร็วหนึ่งลูกของเป้าหมาย (2ครั้งต่อฉาก)(ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่) </AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เขากำลังแบกโลงศพ โลงศพอันใหญ่ที่เอาไว้สรรเสริญพนักงานผู้ไม่มีที่ไป มันยังเล็กไปสำหรับร่างของผู้บริสุทธ์ทั้งหลายที่ถูกสังเวย</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">A single coffin to pay tribute to those who had nowhere to go, wandering with the memory of an empty faith…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Where does one go when they die?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The weight of the butterflies that died in vain would be too great to carry.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">That large coffin, simply too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">The fragile wings will keep fluttering, waiting for the moment to fall asleep.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Request">
      <Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
      <CardName>คำขอ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อไม่มี 'เป้าหมายตามคำขอ' อยู่ ศัตรูที่บรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือกโจมตีโดนเป็นคนแรก จะถูกติดสถานะดังกล่าว 
ทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 3-5 หน่วย ต่อเป้าหมายตามคำขอ
เมื่อบรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือกฆ่าเป้าหมายตามคำขอได้ ฟื้นฟู Stagger Resist ทั้งหมด และได้รับหนังสือเป็น 2 เท่า
</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เป็นอย่างที่ปีศาจบอกไว้ กระสุนนี่เจาะทะลุได้ทุกสิ่งที่ใจปราถนา ตลอดไป.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Some call him a righteous hunter, while others would call him a bloodstained gunman.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The bullets always travel across a straight line, along the horizon.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I simply follow my impulse, pointing my rifle as I like.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The advancing bullet has no morals, no good or evil intent.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Sometimes I helped those in need or fought evil.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Seven">
      <Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กระสุนระดับที่เจ็ด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
สร้างดาเมจด้วยเต๋าโจมตีมากขึ้น 1-7 หน่วย
เมื่อเต๋าโจมตี เสมอหรือชนะในการปะทะ ทำดาเมจเท่ากับค่าลูกเต๋าแก่ฝ่ายตรงข้าม
ในการใช้เพจครั้งที่เจ็ด จะทำการสุ่มเป้าหมาย รวมถึงพันธมิตร</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ปีศาจนั้นทำสัญญาอย่างติดเล่น: กล่าวคือกระสุนนัดสุดท้ายนั้น จะทะลวงผ่านศรีษะของผู้ที่เป็นที่รักของเขา เมื่อเขาได้ยินดังนั้น เขาไม่รอช้า ใช้กระสุนยิงทุกคนที่เข้ารักให้ตายจากไปก่อน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The last bullet will puncture the head of your beloved.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You’re right… This magical bullet can truly hit anyone just like you say.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The bullets will puncture anything you please. Forever.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">No bullet will ever be the last.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Flame">
      <Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เพลิงทมิฬ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
จนจบการต่อสู้ ความทนทาน 'ทนทาน/ประสิทธิภาพต่ำ' ของทุกตัวละคร ถูกเปลี่ยนเป็น 'อ่อนแอ่/ร้ายแรง
ได้รับ 1-2 ว่องไว และ 2-4 กำลัง ในทุกๆฉาก</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>วันหนึ่ง มือปืนได้รับรู้ว่า ปีศาจนั้นไม่ได้ตามเขามาอีกต่อไป เขาสงสัยว่าทำไม แล้วเขาจึงได้รู้สึกตัวว่าดวงวิญญาณของเขา ได้ตกสู่ห้วงนรกไปตั้งแต่จุดเริ่มต้นแล้ว</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Was it despair that he wished for?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">My soul began to burn bit by bit, until it ultimately descended to Hell.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">When one feels there’s nothing left to aim for, their soul falls down to Hell.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The despaired heart couldn’t go out in a passionate flame. It would only burn with a cold fire.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">The despair shall linger around you at all times.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Hod">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ShyLookToday_Face">
      <Abnormality>Today’s Shy Look</Abnormality>
      <CardName>สีหน้าประจำวันนี้</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หน้าของบรรณารักษ์จะเปลี่ยนไปตลอด
ลูกเต๋าจะได้เปลี่ยนแปลงพลังขึ้นอยู่กับหน้าปัจจุบัน (น้อยสุด -2 มากสุด +2)
หน้าโกรธจะดุดันไม่เกรงใจใคร</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>วันหนึ่งท้องฟ้าแจ่มใส ก็เหมือนทุกวันที่เขาจะเอาเสื้อผ้ามาตากแดด เพียงแต่วันนี้เป็นหนังของเขาแทน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m just shy, that’s all. Just shy…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">A sad look doesn’t fit the City.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s very important to express oneself… I guess it is.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Do you know what kind of face you should be making?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Put a big smile on your face, like mine. It’s not so hard, is it?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ShyLookToday_Shy">
      <Abnormality>Today’s Shy Look</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เว้นระยะห่าง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าป้องกันได้รับบวก 1-2 พลัง
เมื่อปักป้องสำเร็จ ทำดาเมจStaggerมากขึ้น 2-7 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>หากมีใครพยายามมองสิ่งที่อยู่หลังหนังนั่น ผลลัพธ์คงไม่สวยเท่าไร บริเวณหลังหนังพวกนั้นเป็นพื้นที่ส่วนบุคคล การไม่ไปรุกล้ำนับได้ว่าเป็นความใจกว้างเพียงน้อยนิดที่นครจะมอบให้ได้</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Please don’t look at what’s behind this. It’s the least you can do…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We need to keep an appropriate distance. Far enough for everyone to be comfortable.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">There’s a line between us, around here. Please stay on the other side of this line, at the very least.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Don’t come any closer. Don’t cross my line…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ShyLookToday_Normalface">
      <Abnormality>Today’s Shy Look</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความเขินอาย</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อใช้เพจเต๋าป้องกันทุกลูกในเพจนั้นได้รับพลังเท่ากับจำนวนเต๋าตั้งรับทุกลูกในเพจดังกล่าง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>การที่ใครสักคนไม่กล้าเปิดหน้าก็คงเป็นความเขินรูปแบบหนึ่ง เมื่ออารมณ์เกิดความสั่นทอนเป็นเวลานานๆ การปิดหน้าจึงเป็นตัวเลือกที่ง่ายกว่า</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m just shy, that’s all. Just shy…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Sorry. You’ll get used to it in time…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Maybe it’s to protect myself.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Sometimes, I’m choked with feelings I can’t describe.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="RedShoes_Kirakira">
      <Abnormality>The Red Shoes</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ระยับแสง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ศัตรูมีโอกาส50% ที่จะเย้ายวน
ศัตรูที่เย้ายวนจะเล็งบรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือกเป็นหลัก และทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 2-4 หน่วย
ได้รับพลังบวก 1-2 หน่วย เมื่อปะทะกับศัตรูที่เย้ายวน</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>รองเท้านี่เคยไร้สีสัน 
มันจะกลายเป็นสีแดงในไม่ช้า.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The red is so vivid, isn’t it simply dazzling?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Once you get rid of that person… The shoes are all yours.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s fine. It won’t be hard to take the shoes off their feet if you chop at their ankles.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Don’t you want to be the one shining the brightest here?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">This glamour should be yours alone.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="RedShoes_Desire">
      <Abnormality>The Red Shoes</Abnormality>
      <CardName>คลั่งไคล้</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[ตัวละครทุกคน]
ตัวละครทุกคนถูกคูณ2 เลือดไหล ของตัวเอง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ฉันหักขาแกทิ้ง แล้วแกจะไม่สามารถรำได้อีกต่อไป</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I should be the one in the spotlight!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Only I should perform an elegant dance…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I’ll make you unable to dance forever.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">If I rendered those legs unusable, could I take the position of the protagonist?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Show me your one last dance.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="RedShoes_Cut">
      <Abnormality>The Red Shoes</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ขวาน</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าฟันได้รับพลังบวก 1-3 หน่วย
หากการโจมตีฟันนั้นไม่ต่อเนื่องกัน ได้รับดาเมจ 2-5 หน่วย (ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ณ จุดหนึ่ง &lt;ปกปิด&gt; ก็ใส่รองเท้านี่, แล้วยิ้มกว้างฉีกทิ้งรูหู มัน เอ่อ..., ก็นะ มันก็แปลกอยู่หรอก. นั่นไม่ใช่การยิ้ม นั่นมัน...</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Hone the axe over and over… So that it can chop them off in one swing.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The desires you’ve amassed… Unravel the emotions you’ve concealed and repressed…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The sanguine red axe… Nothing could be more beautiful.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SpiderBud_Cocoon">
      <Abnormality>Spider Bud</Abnormality>
      <CardName>รังไหม</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตี หากเต๋านั้นทอยได้ค่าสูงสุด เป้าหมายได้รับ อัมพาด,พันธนา,เปราะบาง 1-2 หน่วย ในฉากหน้า (ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ไม่น่าประหลาดใจนัก ไม่มีพนักงานคนไหนอาสาไปเก็บกู้ร่างของเพื่อนร่วมงานที่ถูกคลุมใยเลยสักคน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">What careless fool stepped on my baby?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Few realized that the food inside my cocoons were not dead.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Spider’s poison is unique, it prevents its victim from dying too quickly.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Watch your step. If you didn’t, then watch your head.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">No one dared to save my hunt.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SpiderBud_BabyAtk">
      <Abnormality>Spider Bud</Abnormality>
      <CardName>มื้ออาหาร</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีศัตรูที่ Stagger อยู่ พันธมิตรทั้งหมดฟื้นฟูHP 2-4หน่วย (ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ปีเตอร์ถูกลากไปติดเพดานในไม่กี่อึดใจ พนักงานที่ถูกพันใยห้อยกันเต็มห้องกักกัน เป็นอาหารสุขภาพดีให้แก่ลูกๆแมงมุม</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Rejoice. You will bring joy to my offspring.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Growing children are always hungry.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s all for our survival, it couldn’t be helped.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">It’s relieving to have plenty of food.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Well now, we have a tasty meal ready for consumption… Come, children.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SpiderBud_Dinner">
      <Abnormality>Spider Bud</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความตื่นตัว</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ศัตรูเสียพลังไป 1 หน่วยเมื่อปะทะกับบรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือก
เมื่อชนะการปะทะ มีโอกาส50% ที่เป้าหมายจะได้รับ 1 พันธนา และ เปราะบาง ในฉากหน้า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ดวงตาที่ส่องสว่างในความมืด, ตามหาเหยื่อที่จะนำมาเลี้ยงปากท้องเหล่าลูกแมงมุม</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">To clearly see in the darkness…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It would be troubling to miss my prey.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I can never take my eyes off them. You never know what’ll happen to my offspring…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I shall be precise this time…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Laetitia_Present">
      <Abnormality>Laetitia</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ของขวัญเซอร์ไพรส์</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ฝ่ายตรงข้ามคนแรกที่ปะทะกับบรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือกนั้น จะติดสถานะ 'ต้าวของขวัญ' 
เมื่อ 'ต้าวของขวัญ' ปะทะกับคนอื่นที่ไม่ใช่บรรณารักษ์ที่ถูกเลือก มีโอกาส40% ที่ 'ของขวัญ'จะระเบิด ทำดาเมจ 2-7 หน่วยและติด 2 เลือดไหลในฉากหน้า
เมื่อ'ต้าวของขวัญ'ตาย 'ต้าวของขวัญ'คนใหม่สามารถเกิดขึ้นได้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>และเมื่อเจ้าตัวน้อยพบคนที่ถูกใจ เธอจะให้ของขวัญที่เธอทำขึ้นมาเองกับคนๆนั้น ข้างในมีอะไรไม่บอกหรอกอิอิ!</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">When you open the gift, you’ll be surprised, like WHOA!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">What’s inside the gift? That’s a secret! It’s boring to spoil it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">It’s a heartfelt gift I made myself. I want you to take it!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Whoops… There goes the secret of the gift.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Laetitia_HeartGift">
      <Abnormality>Laetitia</Abnormality>
      <CardName>แกล้งขำกลิ้ง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าอันแรกของ Combat Page ทุกอันที่บรรณารักษ์ใช้ จะทอยเป็นค่าต่ำสุดหรือสูงสุดเท่านั้น
ได้รับดาเมจ 2-7 หน่วยหากทอยได้ค่าต่ำสุด</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ดังนั้นเด็กสาวตัวน้อยจึงได้ตัดสิน! ที่จะอยู่ที่นี่จนกว่าเสียงหัวเราะจะกลับมายังสถานที่แห่งนี้อีกครั้ง!</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Play with me! Join my friends and laugh with us.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">How was my prank? It was fun, wasn’t it? Your face says so!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I don’t hear any laughter… They all look sad.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I want you to be pleased with my pranks!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Laetitia_Friend">
      <Abnormality>Laetitia</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เพื่อนจ้า</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก แอบเอา 'เพื่อนจ้า' ไปใส่ใน Combat Page 1ใบในมือของคุณ (ยกเว้นเพจประเภท[เมื่อใช้เพจ])
หากมีเพจที่เป็น'เพื่อนจ้า'อยู่แล้ว ความสามารถข้างต้นจะไม่ทำงาน
เพจที่เป็น'เพื่อนจ้า' จะได้รับพลังบวก 2-4 หน่วย
ทว่า หากไม่ใช้เพจดังกล่าวภายใน 2 ฉาก ลบเพจนั้นจากการต่อสู้ ทำดาเมจ 2-7 หน่วยแก่บรรณารักษ์</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เธอนั้นเศร้ามากที่ต้องทิ้งเพื่อนเอาไว้ เธอจึงมีความคิดสุดบรรเจิดขึ้นมา!</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I couldn’t leave my dear friends behind… So I came up with a brilliant idea!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t you worry~ Only meanies hurt friends.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">This place will get livelier the more friends I have!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I hope to find lots of friends here too~</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
      <AbnormalityCard ID="BlackSwan_Feather">
      <Abnormality>Dream of a Black Swan</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ขยะเหนอะหนะ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อชนะการปะทะ ติด พันธนา,เปราะบาง,เลือดไหล,อัมพาต 1 หน่วย แก่ศัตรูทุกตัวในฉากหน้า (2 ครั้งต่อฉาก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เอไลจาห์ล้มลงคุกเขา ก่อนที่จะอ้วกทุกอย่างที่ทุกคนอ้วกไว้ก่อนหน้าออกมา</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The lake ripples gently. As if a number of swans just took flight.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I was faced with reality. The things swelling up inside spilt right out.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I began to puke up the thing everyone else was vomiting.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">As if my lungs were stabbed, it bursts forth as I breathe.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I threw up a mixture of blood and green waste.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="BlackSwan_Umbrella">
      <Abnormality>Dream of a Black Swan</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ร่มอันผุพัง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ได้รับบวกความเร็ว 2-3 หน่วย
เมื่อถูกโจมตี มีโอกาส 30% ลบล้างดาเมจที่จะได้รับ นำดาเมจดังกล่าวคูณสอง แล้วทำกลับไปใส่ผู้โจมตีเป็นดาเมจStagger</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เมื่อเชื่อว่าขนของตนจะกลายเป็นสีขาว เจ้าหงส์ดำพยายามถอนคำสาปโดยการทักรอยใบตำแยเข้าด้วยกัน สิ่งที่เหลืออยู่มีเพียงร่มพังๆที่เคยเป็นสมบัติเท่านั้น</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">What happens when the black swan wakes up from dreaming of a white swan?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">All that I had left was the parasol and this brooch.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The sun was too bright, I had to shade it off.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I yearned to have a dream I would never wake up from, but reality was cruel as ever.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="BlackSwan_Family">
      <Abnormality>Dream of a Black Swan</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ครอบครัวแสนรัก</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ได้รับ 6 'เสื้อผ้าตำแย', ซึ่งจะให้เกราะเท่ากับจำนวนของมันเมื่อเริ่มฉากทุกครั้ง เมื่อจบฉาก 'เสื้อผ้าตำแย' จะถูกลดไปทีละหนึ่งอัน</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เธอเริ่มมองหาพี่น้องของเธอ ครอบครัวผู้ซึ่งต้องการ ผ้าตำแย เพื่อให้พ้นจากคำสาป ครอบครัวของเธอที่เธอคอยฝันไฝ่ถึง</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Although they didn’t have anything to pass onto her, they had honesty and diligence as their most valuable treasure.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I believed… that there had to be a way for everyone to be happy.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I thought if I just worked a little harder, things would work themselves out.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">My family, who should have been freed by wearing the nettle clothing…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">We shared happy dreams with each other.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Netzach">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="UniverseZogak_Echo">
      <Abnormality>Fragment of the Universe</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เสียงกังวานจากเบื้องบน</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[ตัวละครทั้งหมด]
ทำดาเมจStagger 5-10 หน่วยแก่ศัตรูทั้งหมด พันธมิตรทั้งหมดฟื้นฟู 5-10 Stagger Resist</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เธอเห็นบทเพลงอยู่ตรงหน้า มันกำลังเข้าใกล้ ยิ่งเวลาผ่านไปมันก็ยิ่งสวยงาม</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Sing. Perform. Human. Song. Ear. Listen.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Sings. Nerves. Focus. Moment. See. Exist.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Eye. Shut. Feel. Grandeur. Come. Happiness. Beyond.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Understand. Perfection. Moment. Know. Knowledge. Our. Meaning. Deliver.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Do. Together. Chant. Song. Enlightenment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="UniverseZogak_Tentacle">
      <Abnormality>Fragment of the Universe</Abnormality>
      <CardName>หนวดชอนไช</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีแทงสำเร็จ ลดค่า Stagger Resist สูงสุดของเป้าหมายไป5% (สูงสุด 50%, ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ในวินาทีที่หนวดของมันแทงเธอ มันดูดเอาความอยากมีชีวิตอยู่ของเธอไปทั้งหมด</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Negative. Attack. Come. Help. Give.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Knowledge. Our. Simple. Give. Relay. None.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Human. Attack. I. Protect. Along. Attack.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Attack. Swift. Impale.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Human. Attack. Soul. Disappear. Gone. Want.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="UniverseZogak_Sing">
      <Abnormality>Fragment of the Universe</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ไม่สามารถหยั่งถึง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ในการโจมตีข้างเดียว มีโอกาส50% ติด 1 อ่อนแรงและตัดกำลัง แก่เป้าหมายในฉากหน้า
โอกาสข้างต้นจะเพิ่มขึ้นทีละ10% เมื่อโจมตีสำเร็จ (ทำสูงสุด 3 ครั้งต่อการโจมตี 1 ชุด, ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ในท้ายที่สุด เขาก็ได้เข้าสู่อาณาเขตแห่ง ‘Fragment of the Universe’ สำเร็จ แต่ทว่า ไม่มีทางที่สมองอันน้อยของเขาจะต้านทานมันได้</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Understand. You. Together. Human. I.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Want. Understand. I. You. Study.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I. Tell. Story. You. Understand. Try.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ChildofGalaxy_Tear">
      <Abnormality>Child of the Galaxy</Abnormality>
      <CardName>หยาดน้ำตา</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
พลังลูกเต๋า +1, เมื่อตาย ตัวละครทั้งหมดได้รับดาเมจเท่ากับ50% ของMax HPของบรรณารักษ์นี้ (สูงสุด 60)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ฉันได้ยินเสียงหายใจและกระซิบจากเขา มาพร้อมกับความมืดสีดำ เหมือนกับคืนแรกที่เจอเขา</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Walk across the Milky Way with me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You’ll become a pebble, and join me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Let’s go back, just like that night.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I’m so glad to meet you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">If you find me crying again, then wipe my tears for me.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ChildofGalaxy_Friend">
      <Abnormality>Child of the Galaxy</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เหรียญตรามิตรภาพ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
จากนี้ 3 ฉาก พันธมิตรทุกคนฟื้นฟูHP เป็น10% ของMax HPตนเมื่อเริ่มฉาก (สูงสุด 12)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ก้อนกรวดส่องประกายเมื่อมันมาอยู่บนมือคุณ มันโยกเยกและจั้กจี้ ท้ายที่สุดมันก็กลายเป็นจักรวาล</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Don’t lose it, and don’t give it to anyone else.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It’s my gift to celebrate our friendship. Please treasure it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">As long as you’re holding it, I’ll be right next to you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You have to stay by my side forever, promise? Don’t forget this.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">If my friend gets hurt… That would be sad.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ChildofGalaxy_Token">
      <Abnormality>Child of the Galaxy</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ก้อนกรวด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มแต่ละฉากจากนี้ เพจสามใบบนมือแบบสุ่ม จะติดสถานะ 'ก้อนกรวด' (ยกเว้นเพจประเภท[เมื่อใช้เพจ])
เมื่อใช้เพจที่ติดก้อนกรวด ฟื้นฟู 3-7 HP
เมื่อใช้เพจที่ไม่ติดก้อนกรวด เสีย 1-3 HP</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“เธอชอบมันไหม? มากกว่าชอบฉันรึเปล่า? มันแน่อยู่แล้วนี่? ฉันรู้ทุกอย่าง ไม่ว่าเธอจะทำอะไร จะไปที่ไหน”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Why did you visit that friend instead… Do you like them more than you like me?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I treasure you, but you won’t treasure me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Whatever you do, wherever you go… I’m always watching everything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">If you won’t keep me company, then I don’t need you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Goodbye, and don’t come back to me again.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Porccubus_Thorn">
      <Abnormality>Porccubus</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ขวากหนาม</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีแทงสำเร็จ ติด 1 เร้าใจ แก่เป้าหมาย
เมื่อโจมตีเป้าหมายที่มีเร้าใจ 3หรือมากกว่า ทำดาเมจและดาเมจStaggerเพิ่มเติม 2-7 หน่วย แล้วลบเร้าใจออกจากเป้าหมายทั้งหมด (ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ครั้งแรก แค่ให้หนามตำสักหนึ่งอันก็มากพอแล้ว แต่ตอนนี้ถ้าอยากไปดึงดาวล่ะก็ ฉันจะต้องเอาทั้งตัวไปถูกับมัน</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Sure, I’ll bend down for you~ Feel free to pet me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It’s scary at first, but the next step won’t be difficult at all.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Come under me. I’ll liberate you from all kinds of pain.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Just a little taste of the heaven won’t hurt, right?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I pity those fools who don’t know this happiness~</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Porccubus_Boom">
      <Abnormality>Porccubus</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ปลืมปิติ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
พลังลูกเต๋า +1, ลด Stagger Resist สูงสุดไป 50%</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ได้เวลาที่หัวฉันจะระเบิดแล้ว ลาก่อย</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">If you wish for unbearable pleasure, you’ll break down eventually.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I’m just giving you laughter, so much that you might die laughing~</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You’ll start with one, and keep wanting more.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Your head will soon be filled with happiness, almost enough to burst your head.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Once you’ve had a taste of this sweetness, you can’t quit.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Porccubus_Happy">
      <Abnormality>Porccubus</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ผงแห่งความตลกโปกฮา</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
เมื่อถูกโจมตี หากไม่ได้Staggerอยู่ ฟื้นฟู 2-4 Stagger Resist (โคตรขำ ตลกมาก 555+)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>หากเศษผงที่ออกมาจากหนามของมันเป็นที่รู้จักขึ้นมา ผู้คนจะจมปรักอยู่ในความมึนเมาไปตลอดกาล</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Your head will soon be filled with happiness.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You’ll fall ill if you hold in your laughter. Why don’t you laugh to your heart’s content?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Laughter makes you happy~ Blessings will come your way, you know?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">If everyone laughs together, they must be in a blissful place, right?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Come on, let’s laugh together~ Turn your mouth all the way up~</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="Alriune_flower">
      <Abnormality>Alriune</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กลีบดอกไม้</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรบุปผา]
เมื่อใดที่บรรณารักษ์รับดาเมจเกิน10% ของMax HPตนเอง ศัตรูทุกคนได้รับดาเมจStagger 4-8 หน่วย บรรณารักษ์ฟื้นฟู 5-10 HP</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ทำได้เพียงสลัดกลีบดอกไม้แทนการร่ำไห้ เธอก็พูดกับฉัน “เราก็เคยเป็นส่วนหนึ่งของพื้นดินมาแล้ว เพราะอย่างนั้น อย่างพึ่งพูดถึงจุดจบของเธอตอนนี้”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I have no eyes, but I can see everything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Let us go back to the grave with all that lives and breathes.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">These flowers bloom without an end, and not one of them would wither.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I am cracked… yet beautiful flowers fill that space.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Alriune_Bush">
      <Abnormality>Alriune</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ก้าวข้ามไบไม้ร่วง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อถูกโจมตี ติด 1 สุคนธรส.
(สุคนธรส: เมื่อเริ่มฉาก รับดาเมจStagger เท่ากับจำนวน'สุคนธรส'ที่มี แล้วหารสองจำนวนของมัน)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เพียงความหวังที่จะสลาย มันจะกลับไปที่หลุมศพพร้อมกับความปราถนาที่จะมีชีวิต</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">My atonement ended with a heavy breath in the cold.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I was abandoned in a dark forest; my mind, life, and heart withering away.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I was born from earth, so now I yearn to return to it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Please don’t think of this as our last moment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Alriune_Doll">
      <Abnormality>Alriune</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ปฐมบทหมื่นบุปผา</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ในทุกฉากจากนี้ ศัตรูหนึ่งตัวจะสุ่มติดสถานะ 'กลีบดอกไม้'
เมื่อตัวละครที่ติดกลีบดอกไม้ถูกโจมตีครบ 4 ครั้งในฉากเดียว ตัวละครทั้งหมดได้รับดาเมจStagger 3-7 หน่วย และในฉากหน้า บรรณารักษ์นี้จะไม่สามารถถูกเลือกเป็นเป้าหมายได้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>บุปผาอันมิอาจร่วงโรย บานสะพรั่งอย่างหามีผู้หยุดยั้ง</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Will you be the one to grant my wish?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">With unwithering flowers began my magnificent descent to despair.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Spring is a season when sins committed anew are forgiven again.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">We only stay in this world for a fleeting moment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SilentOrchestra_Music">
      <Abnormality>The Silent Orchestra</Abnormality>
      <CardName>มหรสพนิรันดร</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เพิ่มเพจ 'มหรสพนิรันดร' เข้ามือ: ‘คอส 3 - [ใช้ครั้งเดียว][เมื่อใช้] จบฉากทันที เมื่อเริ่มฉากใหม่ HPและStagger Resistของผู้ใช้ ถูกย้อนกลับไปเมื่อตอนได้รับเพจนี้ และฟื้นฟูแสงทั้งหมด’
เพจนี้จะถูกรวมเข้าไปในเด็คเมื่อเริ่มองก์ต่อไปด้วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>การแสดงนั้นไม่เคยจบสิ้น แล้วเริ่มต้นใหม่ แล้วเริ่มใหม่แต่ต้น</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">From break and ruin, I begin the most beautiful performance.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">A single performer standing in the midst of a silent score. He creates sounds where there is none.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Even if my hands were to stop, it would rise from your mind.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">This blindingly entrancing stage will be prepared again soon.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
 <AbnormalityCard ID="SilentOrchestra_Affect">
      <Abnormality>The Silent Orchestra</Abnormality>
      <CardName>บูชาอย่างบ้าคลั่ง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
2 ฉากต่อจากนี้ ศัตรูทุกคนจะเล็งเป้าหมายแบบสุ่ม รวมไปถึงพันธมิตรของตัวเองด้วย การโจมตีของศัตรูทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 2-4 หน่วยเมื่อความสามารถนี้ยังอยู่</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>วงออร์เคสตรานั้นทุ่มแรงไปยังเสียงดนตรีนี้อย่างมาก, นำพาทั้งแผนกให้วอดวายไปกับเสียงเพลง เมื่อนักดนตรีทุกคนยืนพร้อมเพียง ท่วงทำนองที่ไร้ผู้ได้ยินแต่มากไปด้วยผู้ฟังจะเริ่มบรรเลง</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The music that no one can hear, but everyone can listen to…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">To the audience who shall walk into their seat upon hearing the choked up performance.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Tune permeates music, and music permeates people.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Don’t lock yourself in, open your eyes to behold the glorious music.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SilentOrchestra_Finale">
      <Abnormality>The Silent Orchestra</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ปิดม่านการแสดง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อบรรณารักษ์ทำให้ศัตรู Stagger ศัตรูทุกคนเสีย 1-6 แสงเมื่อเริ่มฉากหน้า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“บทเพลงนี้จะเจาะทะลวงทั้งร่างกายของเธอ”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The music shall perforate your entire being.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If you can stand with your two legs, be willing to send your praise.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">An endless applause, to inspire the conductor to lift their baton once more.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The beautiful melody circles the empty stage.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Keter">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Blood">
      <Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เลือด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าโจมตีได้รับการเพิ่มพลัง 1-2 หน่วย
ได้รับดาเมจStaggerมากขึ้น 3-5หน่วย.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ความซึมเศร้าอันไม่อาจรับได้นี้ จะมอบให้แก่ใครก็ตามที่ได้มองไปยังอ่างนั่น</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">That person simply couldn’t take her sorrow in stride.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Can you withstand this deep despair?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Come inside. Get into this dreadful pool of blood.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Let go of it all, close your eyes, and sink into this bottomless pool.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">No matter how much blood is added, the bathtub never overflows.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Scar">
      <Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>แผลเป็น</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
รับดาเมจประเภทฟัน น้อยลง 2-5 หน่วย.
เมื่อถูกโจมตี มีโอกาส 20% ลดดาเมจของการโจมตีนั้นเป็น 0</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เมื่อฉันได้เห็นรอยแกะสลักที่ข้อมือเปื้อนเลือดของเธอ ทำให้ฉันนึกถึงลายตู้ไวน์ของเรา วันนั้น ฉันเป็นคนดึงจุกไวน์ขวดสุดท้าย</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">It takes a strong will and courage to cut your own wrist.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t call these people foolish. You’re the biggest coward.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The scars are marks of failure, but they aren’t worthless.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Caress this pain filling the tub softly.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">The depth of a cut depends on the moment’s mind and willpower.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Hands">
      <Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>มือซีดเผือก</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หลังจากโจมตีเป้าหมายเดิมสำเร็จครบสามครั้ง ทำดาเมจStaggerเพิ่มเติม 3-10หน่วย
(นับค่าใหม่เมื่อโจมตีเป้าหมายอื่น, ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>มีมือมากมายลอยอยู่ในอ่าง.
พวกมันคือมือของผู้คนที่ฉันเคยรักใคร่</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The hands of one that you, perhaps we, loved are resting inside.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">These hands are waiting for someone to hold them, would you grant their wishes?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">No matter how much you wish to grasp what slips through your fingers…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">These hands earnestly want help, yet no one bothers to give them a glance.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">She must’ve trembled hard, the knife could slip from her hand at any moment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Heart">
      <Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ชีพจร</CardName>
       <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
ได้รับ 1-2 กำลัง ในทุกๆครั้งเมื่อจบฉากGain 1-2 Strength at the end of each Scene.
เมื่อถึงตอนจบฉาก หากบรรณารักษ์ไม่เคยสร้างดาเมจด้วยเต๋าโจมตีเลยฉากนี้ ลดMax HPของเขาไป25%(สูงสุด30)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ความปราถนาที่มากเกินไป จะนำไปสู่ความบ้าคลั่งที่ไม่อาจเข้าใจได้</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Overwhelming aspiration is what leads to wrongful frenzy.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Why won’t you wish for anything when you’ve earned such power?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">He who holds power should rightfully wield it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Yes, feel the rapid beating of your heart.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">It seems we have a common goal we’re desperately wishing for, so allow us to help.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Doki">
      <Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กระหาย</CardName>
     <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เพิ่มMax HP 15% (เพิ่มHPให้เต็มไปด้วย)
ความเร็วเพิ่มขึ้น 1-2 หน่วย.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เมื่อยืมพลัง มันจะหดตัวเป็น2เท่า และผู้ยืมพลังจะได้รับพละกำลังอันมหาศาล</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Never stop wishing for it, until the beats give an answer.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t you want to see the end of this thrill that’s about to burst?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Give a meaning to all things we’ve wished for.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Join me in this feverish pulsation.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Your craving will make the beats faster.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Atk">
      <Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ชีพจรรุนแรง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
บรรณารักษ์ที่เลือกจะตุยเมื่อจบฉากที่สามที่ได้เลือกเพจนี้
ได้รับ กำลัง,อึดทน,ว่องไว,เกราะ อย่างละ4หน่วยทุกฉากจนตาย Stagger resistทุกรูปแบบถูกเปลี่ยนเป็นประสิทธิภาพต่ำ.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>หัวใจที่ไร้เจ้าของ แม้จะอยู่นอกร่างกาย มันก็ยังคงเต้นอยู่.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Yes, feel the rapid beating of your heart.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If you keep craving and do nothing to sate it, it’ll become too big and burst eventually.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Join me in this feverish and quick pulsation.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Even if it means I must burst someday, I want to see the end of it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">The more you aspire, the faster the beats will get.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Learn">
      <Abnormality>พิน็อกคิโอ</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เรียนรู้</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ได้รับเพจ'ดูให้รู้' เข้ามาในมือ: 'คอส 2 - [เมื่อเริ่มการปะทะ] แทนที่เต๋าในเพจนี้ด้วยเต๋าของเพจศัตรูคู่ปะทะทั้งหมด’
เพจนี้จะถูกเพิ่มเข้าไปในสำรับคุณเมื่อเริ่มองก์ถัดไปด้วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เด็กทุกคนทำได้เพียง'เรียนรู้'โดยการสังเกตคนรอบข้าง แล้วเลียนแบบพฤติกรรมพวกเขา นั่นแหละคือปัญหา</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m keen to learn as usual. Would you like to see me learn?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">People taught me how to speak.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I’m not a fast learner. I just mimic what I see.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">It’s not hard to mimic others. I don’t have to think.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I’ve learned lots of things, but I never go anywhere.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Lie">
      <Abnormality>Pinocchio</Abnormality>
      <CardName>โกหกตดเหม็น</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ทำการสุ่มค่าคอสของเพจทุกใบที่มีค่าคอสเดิมน้อยกว่า 4.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ใครๆเขาก็โกหกกัน มันจะแย่ได้ยังไงจริงไหม?</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">People love to say things the other way round.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">They said it wasn’t for themselves. They were lying for the good of everyone…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Lalala… I sing along to the song of lies all the people sing.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I see the world upside down, as people have taught me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Everyone lies, why are you saying it’s a bad thing?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Curious">
      <Abnormality>Pinocchio</Abnormality>
      <CardName>อยากรู้อยากเห็น</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก นำเพจในมือทุกใบเข้าไปในกองจั่ว จากนั้นจั่ว 4 เพจ</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ฉันกระตือรือร้นในการเรียนรู้เสมอ อยากเห็นฉันเรียนรู้ไหม?</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I still have lots of things I want to know. There’s lots to learn.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If I see various things… Will I learn that much?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I’m curious about this… curious about that… Oh, and what’s this?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I’ve never seen that before… Where did it come from, and how?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

    <AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Sord">
      <Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ดาบเยือกแข็ง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อชนะการปะทะ มีโอกาส50% ติด 1-3 พันธนาแก่อีกฝ่ายฉากหน้าUpon winning a clash, inflict 1-3 Bind next Scene at a 50% chance.
ทำดาเมจStaggerบวก2-5 หน่วยแก่เป้าหมายที่ติดพนธนาainst targets with Bind.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ราชินีอาศัยอยู่อย่างเดียวดายในป่าเหมันต์.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The edge of this blade is sharp and cold.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Only the warmth of spring can melt away this sword.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The straight blade knows exactly where to point itself to.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">One day, when it gets warm enough for snow to melt, this sword shall too thaw away.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">When this weapon impales your heart, you’ll become oblivious of yourself for a moment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Chu">
      <Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
      <CardName>จุมพิต</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อชนะการปะทะ 2ครั้งหรือมากกว่าด้วยCombat pageอันเดียว ติด เสี้ยนน้ำแข็ง แก่เป้าหมาย
เมื่อจบฉากทุกครั้ง ตัวละครที่มีเสี้ยนน้ำแข็ง 3 อันหรือมากกว่าจะหมดสภาพในฉากหน้า
      </AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>จุมพิตของThe Snow Queenแช่หัวใจของเขาให้เยือกเย็น จนเขาไม่รู้สึกถึงความหนาวอีกเลย</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Only those who know of the scent of roses can bring an end to it all.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You must have had a warm heart once.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Forgetting the cold, forgetting the memories, and at last…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Could a frozen heart that’s become numb to the cold thaw out?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Only the fortitudinous shall be able to rescue the frozen.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Snow">
      <Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
      <CardName>พายุหิมะ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ตัวละครทุกตัวยกเว้นบรรณารักษ์ที่เลือก จะหมดสภาพในฉากนี้
ฉากหน้า ศัตรูทุกคนจะได้รับ 6 พันธนา</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ไบไม้ผลินำพามาซึ่งกุหลาบอันผลิบาน ละลายราชวังของSnow Queenจนหมดสิ้น เธอหลับอยู่ภายใต้มัน ไม่มีใครจำเธอได้</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">No one will realize that I am slumbering in this place.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">When this snow melts, I will also be forgotten.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Is my castle melting away, has the warm spring truly arrived…?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The roses’ full bloom signals to me that spring has come.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">That person must not have wished for any more of this cold.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
     <AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Hammer">
      <Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ค้อนและตะปู</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีแทงสำเร็จ ติด 1 ตะปูแก่เป้าหมาย
หากตัวละคนที่มีตะปูถูกโจมตีโดยประเภททุบ เขาจะได้รับดาเมจเพิ่มเติม 5เท่าของจำนวนตะปูทั้งหมด และลบตะปูทั้งหมดในตัวละครนั้น</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เมื่อเธอตอกตะปูด้วยค้อนของเธอ รอยแยกในใจจะกว้างขึ้น และสลายในที่สุด</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I wonder if there’s a crack in your mind that I could hammer a nail in?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">When a nail drives into a fissure, it gets twice as wide.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You should’ve been quick to deal with the baggage in your mind.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">There’s no repair for a mind that has been cracked.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Eyeshine">
      <Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>มองค้อน</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ทำ และได้รับดาเมจกายภาพมากขึ้น2เท่า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>เด็กสาวยังคงเงียบอยู่อย่างนั้น เธอทำเพียงจ้องมองไปยังภายในของผู้คนด้วยตาของเธอ</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">……</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">………</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You’re trembling so much. What makes you so afraid?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Guilty">
      <Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ผิดบาป</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ลดดาเมจStaggerที่จะได้รับ 1-3 หน่วย.
เมื่อถูกโจมตี ผู้โจมตีได้รับดาเมจStagger เท่ากับจำนวนที่ตัวละครนี้ได้รับ</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>ทว่า เมื่อเธอได้พบกับคนที่แบกรับความ'กลัว' หรือ 'ผิดบาป' อยู่เด็กสาวจะหยิบตะปูและค้อนออกมาจากหลังของเธอ</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">You’re still holding onto those painful memories… You poor fellow.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t shove the responsibility on others. The agony is yours to bear.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You were just too busy running away, weren’t you?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Dear, you seem to be quite… unnerved, aren’t you?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Tiphereth">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenOfHatred_Laser">
      <Abnormality>The Queen of Hatred</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความรัก</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หลังชนะการปะทะด้วยเต๋าโจมตี ฟื้นฟูHP พันธมิตร1คนแบบสุ่ม 3-5 หน่วย
หลังชนะการปะทะด้วยเต๋าตั้งรับ ฟื้นฟูStagger Resist พันธมิตร1คนแบบสุ่ม 2-4 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>In the name of Love and Justice~ Here comes Magical Girl!</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Don’t worry. You guys will be safe as long as I’m here!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You can count on me any time! I’ll keep you safe.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">A true magical girl never runs away in the face of any hardships!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Tell me if anything bad happens, okay? I know I can help you! </Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">Please feel free to call me whenever there’s danger~!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenOfHatred_Gun">
      <Abnormality>The Queen of Hatred</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความเที่ยงธรรม</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ศัตรูที่ทำดาเมจแก่พันธมิตรมากที่สุดเมื่อฉากที่แล้ว จะถูกตั้งให้เป็น 'ตัวร้าย'
เมื่อโจมตี 'ตัวร้าย' ทำดาเมจมากขึ้น 3-5 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>If I am on the side of good, then someone has to be on the side of evil. Without someone to play the villain, I can’t exist.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Finally, a villain shows up! Careful, everyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It’s okay. I can take care of the baddies!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">In the name of Love and Justice~ I have arrived!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Those who disrupt society will be brought to justice.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
 <AbnormalityCard ID="QueenOfHatred_Snake">
      <Abnormality>The Queen of Hatred</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความเกลียดชัง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อแพ้การปะทะ ได้รับดาเมจStagger 2-4 หน่วย และได้รับ 1 กำลัง ฉากหน้า(2 ครั้งต่อฉาก)
เมื่อแพ้การปะทะ 3ครั้งในฉากเดียว ลดค่าคอสของเพจที่แพงที่สุดในมือไป 1 หน่วย(1 ครั้งต่อฉาก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>She vowed to love everything in the world, but all that was left was a collapsing heart.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Why is everybody happy? I’d have no reason to exist if they are…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I am the chosen one. Who would protect the world besides me?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I wasn’t able to protect anyone…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I hate a peaceful world… It’s like… It’s like I’m not needed anymore…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I deserve to be everyone’s hero. I was born this way…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="KnightOfDespair_Gaho">
      <Abnormality>The Knight of Despair</Abnormality>
      <CardName>อวยพร</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อตัวละครนี้ได้รับดาเมจจากการโจมตีเมื่อฉากที่แล้ว เลือกประเภทดาเมจที่ได้รับมากที่สุด แล้วเปลี่ยนความทนทานของประเภทดาเมจนั้นให้เป็น 'ทนทาน' ตลอดฉากนี้ (ดาเมจกายภาพและดาเมจStagger จะคำนวณแยกกัน)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The will to protect seems to remain unchanged after all this time; even in containment, it is still obsessed with the act of protection.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">All that remains is the hollow pride of a weathered knight.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If I could have another chance to protect…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Worry not. I’ll keep you safe this time.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">To sleep in peace…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="KnightOfDespair_Sword">
      <Abnormality>The Knight of Despair</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ดาบที่ลับคมโดยหยาดน้ำตา</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีแทงสำเร็จ หากทอยเต๋าได้ค่าสูงสุด ทำดาเมจเพิ่มเติมเท่ากับ 10% ของMax HPเป้าหมาย(สูงสุด 12 ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>When Justice turns its back once more, several dozen blades will rove without a purpose. The swords will eventually point at those she could not protect.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The edge of this sword sharpened with tears and despair is always precise.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I vowed to this sharp sword, whetted with tears on an anvil of despair.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Foul play is forbidden. There won’t be any mercy, either…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="KnightOfDespair_Despair">
      <Abnormality>The Knight of Despair</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความสิ้นหวัง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
เมื่อพันธมิตรตาย พันธมิตรคนอื่นๆ ได้รับ 1-3 กำลังและว่องไว และศัตรูทุกคนติด 2 เปราะบาง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>As with sorrow, perhaps sharing the burden will blunt the edge.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The despair swelling up inside me is now overflowing through my eyes and heart…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">What does this despair… mean to me?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Why must I lose others again and again… Why…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Yet again, endless despair fills me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I swore to protect, yet I lost them again…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Greed_Break">
      <Abnormality>The King of Greed</Abnormality>
      <CardName>มากจนไม่สมดุล</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หากเต๋าแรกของ Combat Page ชนะการปะทะ มีโอกาส 25% ทำลายเต๋าที่เหลืออยู่ของฝ่ายตรงข้ามทั้งหมด</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The first seed of desire originated from the pure yearning for happiness. The tiny seed grew larger and larger, hungering for more. Over time, the seed hardened and turned into a piece of shiny gem.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">A thought echoed inside my head. A thought soaked with greed, compelling me to pursue happiness.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Is it so bad to lust for honey when there are flowers?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">At first, it was a pure longing for happiness.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The yearning for happiness would remain the same.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Greed_Protect">
      <Abnormality>The King of Greed</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เส้นทางสู่ความสุข</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ได้รับ 1 อึดทน เมื่อชนะการปะทะ (ได้สูงสุด 3 ครั้งต่อฉาก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Happiness became obsession, obsession became greed, and the greed forever solidified to become a golden amber. The happiness in the beginning, still holding a smile, dwells inside.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">At last, the once pure desire materialized into golden amber and solidified.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">This greed shall forever shine brilliantly.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">How can one resist the allure of this gorgeous being.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Wishing for everyone’s happiness must include my own, too…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Greed_Eat">
      <Abnormality>The King of Greed</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความโลภ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ในการปะทะ หากเต๋าของผู้ชนะทอยได้จำนวนมากกว่าผู้แพ้ 4 หน่วยหรือมากกว่า ผู้แพ้ได้รับความเสียหายเพิ่มเติม 3-7 หน่วย และผู้ชนะฟื้นฟูHP 2-5 หน่วย (ทั้งบรรณารักษ์และฝ่ายตรงข้าม ได้รับผลจากความสามารถนี้ทั้งคู่)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The magical girl, who was no longer a magical girl, ate many things. Authority, money, fame, and many other forms of pleasure. She ended up eating away anything in her sight. Now, only visceral greed remains.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The gem fanned the starved greed.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">But greed seeks eternity—seeks deep, deep eternity.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">My basket is so large, all the fruits of the world can’t make it full.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Nothing was left in my wake. Only visceral greed remained.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="Angry_Angry">
      <Abnormality>The Servant of Wrath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ความแค้น</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
บรรณารักษ์ที่เลือกจะเข้าสู่สถานะ 'เครียดแค้น'
คุณจะไม่สามารถควบคุมบบรรณารักา์คนนั้นได้ และเล็งเป้าไปที่ตัวละครแบบสุ่ม รวมถึงพันธมิตรด้วย
นอกจากนั้น เขาจะได้รับ 2 กำลัง ฟื้นฟูแสง 2 หน่วย และจั่วเพจเพิ่มขึ้น 2 ใบเมื่อเข้าฉากจากนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The Servant was betrayed after abandoning her principles and ingenuously trusting someone with her whole heart. Now, she is dominated by the anger towards herself for what she had done.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">GRRRR!!!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">UUUGH… AAARGH!!!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">AAAAH!!!!!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">SINNERS OF THE OTHERWORLDS!!! EMBODIMENTS OF EVIL!!!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
<AbnormalityCard ID="Angry_Friend">
      <Abnormality>The Servant of Wrath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>พวกพ้อง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อไม่มี 'พวกพ้อง' ทำให้ศัตรูคนแรกที่บรรณารักษ์คนนี้โจมตีนั้น เป็น'พวกพ้อง'เมื่อบรรณารักษ์คนนี้ฆ่าพวกพ้องได้ บรรณารักษ์ทุกคนฟื้นฟูแสง 3 หน่วยและฟื้นฟู HP กับ Stagger Resist 10 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The Servant of Wrath valued justice and balance more than anyone, but she began sharing knowledge with the Hermit—an enemy of her realm—becoming friends with her in secret.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Call me… Call my name…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Friend… My friend… Those who need… each other…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">We… We were true friends… Right?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">It was the most precious relationship to me, and what happened…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Angry_Poison">
      <Abnormality>The Servant of Wrath</Abnormality>
      <CardName>โคลนสารพิษ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[All Enemies]
ติด 5 'กัดกร่อน' แก่ศัตรูทุกคน. ศัตรูจะได้รับ พันธนา เท่ากับจำนวน กัดกร่อน ที่พวกเขามีอีกด้วย
(กัดกร่อน: เมื่อจบฉาก ได้รับดาเมจเท่ากับจำนวน กัดกร่อน และลบมันไป 1 หน่วย เมื่อถูกโจมตี ได้รับดาเมจและดาเมจStaggerเพิ่มเติมเท่ากับจำนวน กัดกร่อน ที่มี)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>When the two met at last, the Hermit brought countless minions to destroy the Servant’s world.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Balance crumbles, and justice vanishes…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">That’s why I lost; I fell to my beloved companion.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Use them and they use you. That’s us.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">This has happened before… Thwarted everything for the sake of them…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NihilClown_Card">
      <Abnormality>The Jester of Nihil</Abnormality>
      <CardName>สาวน้อยเวทมนตร์</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก Combat Page ที่คอสสูงสุดในมือ(ไม่สูงกว่า4) ถูกทำเครื่องหมายตราเวทมนตร์เอาไว้
เมื่อแพ้การปะทะด้วยเพจดังกล่าว 4ครั้ง ได้รับ 5 เกราะทุกๆฉาก และสถานะทางลบจะไม่มีผลไปจนจบ Reception
และเมื่อถูกโจมตี ติด 1 กัดกร่อนและเปราะบาง ในฉากหน้าแก่ผู้โจมตี (2 ครั้งต่อฉาก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The jester retraced the steps of a path everybody would’ve taken. The jester always found itself at the end of that road. There was no way to know if they had gathered to become the jester, or if the jester had come to resemble them.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Did you make me, or did I make you?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I look just like them, and they look just like me when they’re together.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I slowly traced the road back. It’s the road you would’ve taken.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NihilClown_Nihil">
      <Abnormality>The Jester of Nihil</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ว่างเปล่า</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เพิ่มเพจ 'จงกลับสู่ความว่างเปล่า' เข้าสู่มือ : ‘คอส 3 - [ใช้ครั้งเดียว;][เมื่อเริ่มการต่อสู้] สลายการ์ดบนมือทั้งหมด ทุกฉากต่อจากนี้ จะได้รับ กำลังและอึดทน เท่ากับจำนวนการ์ดที่สลายไปด้วยความสามารถนี้’
เพจนี้จะถูกรวมเข้าไปในเด็คเมื่อเริ่มองก์ถัดไปด้วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The jester was deeper in thought, that poor jester. Without the brave puppy to lead the way, it walks with meaningless steps.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Where is the right path? Where do I go?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I don’t know what awaits me ahead. Could it be a cliff, or a ditch?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Where is that bright dog when I need it to lead me?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">My mind is a void, my thoughts empty. I become more fearless as they become more vacant.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NihilClown_fusion">
      <Abnormality>The Jester of Nihil</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ต้องห้าม</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เพจนี้จะมีผลได้ หากบรรณารักษ์มี Abnormality pages เหล่านี้ทั้งหมดเท่านั้น: 'ความโลภ', 'ความเกลียดชัง', 'ความสิ้นหวัง', และ 'ความแค้น'
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ติด อ่อนแรง,ตัดกำลัง,พันธนา 5 หน่วย แก่ตัวละครอื่นๆทุกตัว ลบข้อเสียของเพจ 'ความโลภ', 'ความเกลียดชัง', 'ความสิ้นหวัง', and 'ความแค้น' อย่างสิ้นเชิง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Having decided to trust its own intuition, the jester spake the names of everyone it had met on that path with each step it took.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Leading the way through foolishness, there’s not a thing to guide me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Blinded by carnal desires and jealousy, willingly walking to the edge of the cliff.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">If you’re confused because there doesn’t seem to be a correct method at the moment, just trust your intuition!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Everybody’s agony becomes one.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>


  <Sephirah SephirahType="Gebura">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Redhood_Hunt">
      <Abnormality>Little Red Riding Hooded Mercenary</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เหยื่อ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หลังเลือกเพจ เล็งศัตรูคนแรกที่โจมตีบรรณารักษ์ที่เลือกเอาไว้
เมื่อโจมตีศัตรูดังกล่าว ทำดาเมจเพิ่มเติ่ม 2-6 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The wolf’s death is the one and only thing I can love in my life.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m a pro. I can handle that easily.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Don’t take your eyes off it. Fix your sight upon its movement.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Once you’ve set your sights on a target, commit to your hunt. Don’t give up.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Fix your gaze upon your target and run at it. Have the resolve to kill it, whatever it takes.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">If you make a request, then I might help you.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Redhood_Revenge">
      <Abnormality>Little Red Riding Hooded Mercenary</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ชำระแค้น</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ได้รับ กำลัง โดยขึ้นอยู่กับดาเมจที่ได้รับในฉากที่แล้ว (1 กำลัง ต่อ 5 ดาเมจ, สูงสุด 2 ครั้ง)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Between us, there’s no victory to be won. All I think about is how I’ll kill that bastard in a way more gruesome and painful than the last time.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’ve been grinding the blade to behead that damned wolf.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Hand that dreadful, cunning bastard over to me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I’ll hang his head over my bed. Only then can I get up in the morning without having a nightmare.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">It was all to read the enemy. Now’s the time to return the favor.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Redhood_RedScar">
      <Abnormality>Little Red Riding Hooded Mercenary</Abnormality>
      <CardName>รอยเฆี่ยนสีดินแดง</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หากHPของบรรณารักษ์ เป็น 50%/35%/25% หรือต่ำกว่า, ได้รับ 1/2/4 กำลัง ในแต่ละฉากจากนี้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>I got used to grinding the axe instead of picking flowers when I was 15.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">This isn’t a proud decoration of a survivor. It’s the proof of my will to live.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The more scars you get, the stronger your will to survive becomes.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Don’t take pride in it. It’s a sign that you weren’t skilled enough.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">…I feel horrible when I look at these scars. It makes me shudder in fury.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
     <AbnormalityCard ID="BigBadWolf_Claw">
      <Abnormality>Big and Will be Bad Wolf</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กรงเล็บอำมหิต</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
หลังจากบรรณารักษ์ได้รับดาเมจที่มากกว่า25% ของMax HPตน ในฉากหน้า จะไม่สามารถถูกเลือกเป็นเป้าหมาย และไม่สามารถปะทะได้
และบรรณารักษ์ได้รับ 2 กำลัง ในฉากนี้ และเมื่อโจมตีสำเร็จแต่ละครั้ง ติด 1 เลือดไหล แก่เป้าหมาย </AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Once upon a time, these claws would cut open the bellies of numerous creatures and tear apart their guts.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">What sharp claws I had, the better to fill the role I was born for…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The wolf was born to do bad things and be punished accordingly…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">These violent and savage claws would always tear into the skin of fresh meat…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Nothing was better than these claws at tearing apart someone’s guts…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="BigBadWolf_Eat">
      <Abnormality>Big and Will be Bad Wolf</Abnormality>
      <CardName>สัญชาตญาณ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อใดหากบรรณารักษ์ที่เลือก ชนะการปะทะ เต๋าสุดท้ายในเพจปัจจุบันจะได้รับ พลัง เพิ่ม 1-2 หน่วย
หากเต๋าสุดท้ายดังกล่าวโจมตีสำเร็จ ฟื้นฟู 3-7 HP</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The taste of flesh was so good after such a long absence. Since then, it got harder and harder to keep himself in check. Still, it didn’t matter to him. After all, he was “destined” to be a big bad wolf.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">This place reeks of an awful stench… It calls for me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Like the empty moon filled with darkness, my belly should be filled with meat…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Looking at you makes my mouth water…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">If I can fill my stomach… I’ll be satisfied…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="BigBadWolf_Change">
      <Abnormality>Big and Will be Bad Wolf</Abnormality>
      <CardName>บทบาทของหมาป่า</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าโต้กลับ ได้รับ พลัง เพิ่ม 1-2 หน่วย
เมื่อเต๋าโต้กลับชนะการปะทะ ติด 2 เปราะบางแก่เป้าหมาย (3 ครั้งต่อฉาก)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Wolves could not cross the line when doing bad things. And wolves had to be punished. Wolves always needed to be an example.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Doesn’t matter… I’m destined to be a big bad wolf…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Everyone called me that, so it must be true… Old tales are never wrong…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">A wolf needs no name, it just obeys the role it was born to fit in…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">No one ever wished to get close to the scary wolf…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="Mountain_Eat">
      <Abnormality>Mountain of Smiling Bodies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>การดูดกลืน</CardName>
<AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
จนจบองก์นี้ เมื่อฆ่าศัตรูได้ ฟื้นฟูHP20% ของMax HPตน (สูงสุด 20)
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ได้รับ กำลัง โดยขึ้นอยู่กับจำนวนHP ที่บรรณารักษ์เคยฟื้นฟูมาในองก์นี้ทั้งหมด (1 กำลังต่อ 10%ของMax HPที่ฟื้นฟู, สูงสุด 3 กำลัง)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>It only wants one thing: our flesh drenched in blood. Once it gets a whiff of the scent, it will pursue us in an instant.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Meat… Tasty… me…at…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The smell… this… way…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Not… enough… must eat… more…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">More bodies… will… make us… stronger…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Mountain_Shout">
      <Abnormality>Mountain of Smiling Bodies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>หัวเราะชอบใจ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อบรรณารักษ์ถูกโจมตีตอนที่HP ของตนเป็น50% หรือต่ำกว่า มีโอกาส50% ที่จะกรีดร้องคลื่นเสียงออกมา (สูงสุด 3 ครั้งต่อฉาก)
การกรีดร้อง ทำดาเมจStaggerแก่ศัตรูทุกคน 2-5 หน่วย และติด 1 เปราะบาง แก่พวกเขาในฉากหน้า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>From the mountains of bodies; the dead gave life to something. The dead fused with one another, all smiling.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Krrrh… Ghh… Grgh…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We help… each other… Sharing with each other… our hands… and feet…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">All… are smiling… we… are happy…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">We are… together… helping…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Mountain_Vomit">
      <Abnormality>Mountain of Smiling Bodies</Abnormality>
<CardName>ภูเขาแห่งซากศพ</CardName>
<AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อเลือกเพจนี้ บรรณารักษ์ทุกคนยกเว้นคนที่เลือก จะถูกฆ่าโดยทันที
จนจบการต่อสู้ บรรณารักษ์ที่เลือกจะได้รับ จำนวนแสงสูงสุด,อัตราฟื้นแสง,กำลัง,เกราะ และว่องไว เป็นจำนวนเท่ากับบรรณารักษ์ที่ตายด้วยความสามารถข้างต้น</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The more bodies it comes across, the more defined its shape becomes. And it is never satisfied.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Must… must become one… again…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Must return… Must… hurry…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">No… This is… not… good…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Don’t fall off… Get together again… We are one…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Nosferatu_BloodHope">
      <Abnormality>Nosferatu</Abnormality>
      <CardName>กลัวน้ำ</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตี ติด 1 เลือดไหล แก่เป้าหมายในฉากหน้า คุณได้รับ 1 โลหิต (ไม่นับการโจมตีหมู่)
โลหิตจะให้ผลต่างๆขึ้นอยู่กับจำนวนของมัน เช่นทำดาเมจมากขึ้นแลกกับเสียHP, รับดาเมจStaggerเมื่อเริ่มฉาก, ได้รับ กำลัง เป็นต้น</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>He seemed lost. He was looking for something, but he didn’t appear to know what he wanted to find.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Blood… I want vivid blood!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">A night when one is allowed to pursue all kinds of desire… A neverending, blood-red night.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The blood—in its purest and clearest form! Bring me eternal happiness!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The Danse Macabre is with everyone! All and sundry have a fair chance of being eaten!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Nosferatu_Wine">
      <Abnormality>Nosferatu</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ไวน์</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อฆ่าศัตรูที่ติดเลือดไหล พันธมิตรทุกคนฟื้นฟู 10 HP และบรรณารักษ์ที่เลือก ได้รับ โลหิต จำนวนสูงสุด</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>It maintains a human form, but a single drop of blood should be enough for it to shapeshift into a ferocious monster and spend the night in a rampage.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Ah… Holding back the pain of this thirst is not exactly a pleasing sight to behold.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">It’s too early for a nap… Won’t you join me and share the pleasure?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Forfeit false hope, and forget about the pretense of humanity…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Tempted by raging thirst, the glass is emptied.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Nosferatu_Vampire">
      <Abnormality>Nosferatu</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ผีดูดเลือด</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เมื่อโจมตีเป้าหมายที่ติดเลือดไหล ฟื้นฟูHPตน 2-5 หน่วย และทำดาเมจเพิ่ม 2-4 หน่วย</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>…And the thirst would never truly be quenched.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Death dances macabrely with everybody! All of you have a fair chance to be consumed!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Time for a feast! Enjoy the blood-red night imbued with madness to your heart’s content!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">There is no escape from this thirst!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Chew it all up! Imbibe to the last drop!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NothingThere_Goodbye">
      <Abnormality>Nothing There</Abnormality>
      <CardName>ลาฮ้าฟสุดสวย</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
เต๋าสุดท้ายที่บรรณารักษ์ใช้ในฉาก จะเพิ่มพลังเป็น2เท่า</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>If it has been confirmed that it has escaped and stood on two feet, there is only one thing you can do. Straighten up your posture, gather your hands neatly, and pray to whatever you believe in and observe the situation as it unfolds.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Help…me… Hel… HELP ME!!!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Is anyone… nyone… there?! ANYONE THERE!!!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Do… n‘t wan… D… don’t wanna… I don’t wanna die…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Hello. Hell-o. He… llo… Hello.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NothingThere_Hello">
      <Abnormality>Nothing There</Abnormality>
      <CardName>หวัดดีฮ้าฟ?</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ในทุกๆฉาก เต๋าแรกที่บรรณารักษ์ใช้ จะฟื้นฟูHP เท่ากับดาเมจที่มันทำได้</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“What’s worse, it tried to mimic humans. Doing stuff like looking into a mirror, mumbling to itself, or trying to fix its skeletal structure; it’s as if it was trying to mimic ‘us’.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Mon… ster. That… mons… ter… That monster… why is it here…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">…er!!! …ger!!! Save… me!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Th… Tha… horr… ible… monster… monster…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">el… llo… Hello? ello… Hello?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="NothingThere_Skin">
      <Abnormality>Nothing There</Abnormality>
      <CardName>เปลือก</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
ลบล้างดาเมจStagger จากการโจมตีอย่างสิ้นเชิง</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Its appearance resembles a human, but it most certainly isn’t human. It periodically devours employees and wears their shell. The skeleton and organs are misplaced during the process, so it takes a bizarre form.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Love… Lo… ou… I love you…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Want… a shell… Shell…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Than… k you… Thank you. Thank you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Cool… Cool. Cool.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>

  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Chesed">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ScareCrow_Wisdom">
      <Abnormality>Scarecrow Searching for Wisdom</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Torn Off Wisdom</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Whenever the librarian uses a page, discard a random page from hand and restore 1 Light. (Excludes [On Play] pages)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>When he returned, he had a visibly long scar on his head. People asked him how he felt, and he responded that his head felt lighter.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Wisdom… Give me the wisdom I lack…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">My head is all empty… I’m just a dowdy pile of hay…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">People often talk without thinking… I could make better use of those brains…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I wonder how it feels to be wise… To know everything…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="5">I’m fine with detaching the head if it can get better once it comes back together…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Scarecrow_Harvest">
      <Abnormality>Scarecrow Searching for Wisdom</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Gleaning</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
After attacking an enemy with a higher amount of Stagger Resist, deal 2-4 bonus Stagger damage, and recover 2-5 Stagger Resist.(Excludes Mass Attacks)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>It shows aggression towards certain employees, attempting to take their brains. These employees are those who scored “Excellent” on the intelligence test.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I feel much smarter… I can know anything now…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Good… Very good… I’ll be smarter the more I eat, right…?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Have I become wiser…? Maybe I’ll be more than a stack of hay…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Scarecrow_Rake">
      <Abnormality>Scarecrow Searching for Wisdom</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Rake</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
After Staggering an enemy, copy two pages owned by that enemy and add them to the librarian's hand with 2 less Cost.
The copied pages are exhausted on use.
(Can only copy Melee pages while equipping a Melee-only Key page, and vice versa; no effect against characters with 'Shimmering')</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The rake tilled the human brain instead of farmland. How many of the wise people among us have lost their lives to this rake?</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’ll scrape your wisdom…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I want to be smart like the others…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The wisdom to move forward… I want it…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LumberJack_Cut">
      <Abnormality>Warm-hearted Woodsman</Abnormality>
      <CardName>A Warm Heart</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
At the start of the Scene, boost the Power of Offensive dice by +1-2 for the Scene if the librarian has 3 or more Light.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>In anger, he swung his axe through the wizard’s heart. The warm heart was pulsing vigorously.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">This is… how it feels to have a thumping heart…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The louder the heart echoes… the faster I move…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The kinder the owner of the heart was… the warmer my insides become…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">The heart is a peculiar thing… I can laugh now…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LumberJack_Tree">
      <Abnormality>Warm-hearted Woodsman</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Timber</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
When attacking a target that has more Light than the librarian, Offensive dice gain Power equal to the amount of Light the target has. (Up to 2)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>This is a forest full of hearts. No matter how many he cuts down, the forest still remains dense.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I chop, and chop… Yet the forest remains dense…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I want to be warm… I need something stronger…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I crammed all I could find into this empty canister… yet it is… still cold…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">To cut more trees, I never neglected sharpening the axe…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LumberJack_Heart">
      <Abnormality>Warm-hearted Woodsman</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Cardiae</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
After dealing 15 or more damage to enemies in a single Scene, reduce the Cost of the two most expensive pages in hand by 1.
On kill, reduce the Cost to 0 instead.
The Cost reduction is reset when the pages are used.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>There will never be enough hearts. Once a Woodsman, he now fells people instead of trees.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I require an object… to fill this empty void…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I do not want to feel this empty and lonely feeling anymore…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The heart made of lead… was stiff and cold.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I clutched my empty chest and grieved…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

   <AbnormalityCard ID="House_LionAtk">
      <Abnormality>The Road Home</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Courage</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
At the start of the Scene, gain Strength and Protection equal to the number of allies currently alive subtracted by 2. (If the value is less than 0, Feeble and Fragile will be inflicted instead.)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Can I follow you forever? So I can tear them apart…</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Friend. I have nothing to fear when I have you around!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We set off with everyone~ Dancing along the road!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Friend. Oh, friends~! Let’s not be scared!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">There’s nothing that can stop us!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="House_BigHouse">
      <Abnormality>The Road Home</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Home</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
At the start of the Scene, numbered targets are placed on up to 3/2/2/1/1 enemies, depending on the number of allies currently alive.
Each time a target is attacked in the correct order, increase outgoing damage by 3 for the Scene.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Unable to ever go back home, they began an endless journey.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Don’t bother us! Let us go home in peace!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Ah~ That wizard! That wicked wizard!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The mean wizard took my friends!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Friends. Oh, friends. Will we get to go home?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="House_Home">
      <Abnormality>The Road Home</Abnormality>
      <CardName>A Road Walked Together</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
If an ally redirects an attack that was initially targeting this character, dice on that ally's page gain 1-2 Power in the clash.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Let’s walk together. To a wonderful land… The world of dreams.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I was sound asleep, then the adventure suddenly began.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Hoyoyo~ Let’s go, together~!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Let’s skip home together!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">There must be a beautiful wonderland at the end of the road…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Ozma_Boom">
      <Abnormality>Ozma</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Power of the Past</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Increase the Cost of Combat Pages by 1.
All dice gain 3-4 Power.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Ozma held the pumpkin-carving knife, then took off running towards where the lady wizard should be.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I’m Ozma… A single person took everything away from me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I don’t want to live a life of being thieved any longer…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I want you to feel it all the same… The misery of forgetting it all… losing it all…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I’ll be the one to take things away this time…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Ozma_forgotten">
      <Abnormality>Ozma</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Oblivion</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add an 'Oblivion' page to hand: ‘Cost 3 - [Single-use;][On Play] Immobilized for this Scene; cannot be targeted. At the end of this Scene, recover 40% of Max. HP (up to 48) and fully restore Light.’
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>There was such a fine and beautiful person, staring at her with a perplexed expression.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Why did I trust a stranger so naively… Why…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I haven’t even touched my face… I was so afraid…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Staying alive is all I can do in a life like this…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">A forgotten being stuck in the underground… Why did it have to be…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Ozma_Immortal">
      <Abnormality>Ozma</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Powder of Life</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
When a librarian takes lethal damage, nullify it and recover 20% of Max. HP (up to 24). Can only activate once per reception.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Finally, she sprinkled cinnamon powder—her favorite—and clutched the pumpkin in her arms.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">All I have left now… are these children.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Here, child… I’ll give you new life.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Come back to me, so I won’t be lonely…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">No… Don’t take away what is mine, not again…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Oz_Emerald">
      <Abnormality>The Adult who Tells Lies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Emerald</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add an 'Emerald' page to hand: ‘Cost 5 - [On Play;] [Target Enemy] Cancel 2 random Combat Pages on the target's Speed dice. Recover 1 Light for each successful hit on the target this Scene (Up to 2)’.
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Oz came up with a brilliant idea. Her emerald eyes seemed to shine even brighter.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The emerald roads sparkle bright as ever.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">She was a poor, poor child… Her eyes were just like mine.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Follow along this path. You might just find what you want.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I’ll make your wishes come true. What do you wish for?</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Oz_Gift">
      <Abnormality>The Adult who Tells Lies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>False Present</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
Add 0-Cost false present pages that activate on play to the E.G.O pages list: 'Liquid Courage', 'Silk Sack of Sawdust', 'Heart of Lead', 'Home that Cannot Be Reached', and 'Transformation'.
The false present pages are also added to the E.G.O page list at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Poor Ozma. She didn’t know that lying adults don’t approach others without reason.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Come closer. I’ll help you forget all of your woes and worries.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">You’re a machine, aren’t you? A heart is unnecessary for a machine.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Drink this potion, it’ll give you courage. You’ll be braver than anyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Wear this pair of shoes and be on your way. To the hometown you miss so much.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Oz_Control">
      <Abnormality>The Adult who Tells Lies</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Magic Trick</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add a 'Magic Trick' page to hand: ‘Cost 4 - [On Play] Reduce the Cost of all pages in hand to 0. When used, their Cost is reset to the value before this effect was applied.’
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Soon, Oz came to be called a wizard by the people.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Poor stuffing of straw. I’ll give you the wisdom to ponder over anything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Tin-cold woodsman. I’ll give you the heart to forgive and love anyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Cowardly kitten. I’ll give you the courage to stand up to anything and everything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Last of all, road that is lost. I will send you home.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
  
  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Binah">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bigbird_Eye">
      <Abnormality>Big Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Watchful Eyes</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Fully restore the selected librarian's Light.
Each Scene, a random ally gains no Light while the selected librarian restores 1 additional Light.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The eyes always shone brilliantly, burning like stars in the night sky. But it gave its eyes to the Big Bird in order to protect the forest.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">For every creature in the forest I saved, my eyes gained another in number.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I need eyes that can check the surroundings thoroughly, in order to keep this place safe.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I won’t miss the smallest creature…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You don’t have to worry. I’ll keep you safe…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bigbird_Lamp">
      <Abnormality>Big Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Eternally Lit Lamp</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Any enemy this librarian targets will be forced to target the librarian back, regardless of Speed.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“If I kill the creatures first, then no one would be killed by the beast!”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Follow this lamp. I’ll save you all.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Giving up my feathers… I gained a light that would burn forever.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Come over here. Let me help you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Let’s brighten the road ahead, so I can have a good view of the lives I must save.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bigbird_Save">
      <Abnormality>Big Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Salvation</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
All dice gain +1 Power against enemies with higher Speed.
If target's HP is at 25% or lower, destroy all of their dice upon winning a clash.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>To this bird, death in itself is salvation.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">If I kill them first, then no one would be killed by the beast!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">A big, scary monster lives in this forest! Be careful.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">A child in peril needs my protection.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">For the weak and powerless… I should take the lead.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SmallBird_Punishment">
      <Abnormality>Punishing Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Punishment</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
After taking damage, the first die of the first page the librarian uses next Scene gains 2-4 Power. (Excludes [On Play] pages)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“It must be because there’s no one to punish people for their misdeeds. If someone takes that role, then no foul act would happen in this world ever again!”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">If I punished them, then there won’t be any more bad people, right?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">There’s no point in forgiving. A misdeed is a misdeed.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">That’s it! It’s gotta be because there’s no one to punish all the bad guys in the world.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="SmallBird_Beak">
      <Abnormality>Punishing Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Punishing Beak</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
The librarian's attacks deal bonus damage equal to the number of Scenes that pass without the librarian taking damage from attacks. (Max. 10)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>People have been committing sins since long ago. “Why do they commit sins, knowing it’s wrong?”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Why do they commit sins when they know it’s wrong?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I’ll give them a good scolding, so they won’t even think about doing misdeeds again.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Don’t do bad things from now on!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Smallbird_Fly">
      <Abnormality>Punishing Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Small Flutters</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Evade dice gain 1-2 Power.
Upon winning a clash using Evade dice, the next Offensive die gains 1-2 Power.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>A small and confident bird that punishes the evil, guilty, and all sorts of irreverent people.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I left the forest, and never went back.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Let’s fly high. Let’s hope that the world will change for the better.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">My flutters might be what it takes to change the world!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">With excitement, I flapped my wings busily.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LongBird_Sin">
      <Abnormality>Judgement Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>The Weight of Sin</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Whenever a die this librarian plays rolls the minimum value, take 2-7 damage and gain 1-2 Strength and Endurance next Scene.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Its scale would never neglect the weight of even the smallest sin.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Time to weigh your sins.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I won’t neglect the weight of any sin.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The weight of your sins will determine the weight of your punishment.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
   <AbnormalityCard ID="LongBird_Scale">
      <Abnormality>Judgement Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Tilted Scale</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
After attacking the enemy with the most HP, recover the HP of the ally with the least HP by 2-8. (3 times per Scene, Excludes Mass Attacks)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>All that remains is the unjust scale. The long bird continues on, doling out judgement.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">This scale always yields a clear verdict; I can make sound, precise judgement with it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">My subjective views might affect fair judgement.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">What if the scale doesn’t tip in either direction someday…? I can’t let that happen.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">My scale won’t cease its duty until the day all evil beings disappear.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
      
    <AbnormalityCard ID="LongBird_Judgement">
      <Abnormality>Judgement Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Judgement</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
At the start of the Scene, ตัวละครทั้งหมด gain 1 Sin at a 50% chance.
If a character has 5+ Sin, they take damage equal to 10% of their Max. HP at the start of the Scene, and all Sin is removed from them.
Sin can be transferred to another character by attacking and damaging them. (Once per page)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Then somebody said, “But what if the scale doesn’t tip in either direction someday?” Worried, Long Bird made a scale that always tipped to one side. That way every judgement would yield a clear verdict.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">When I lift this scale, I wish for immortality upon the guilty.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I will pass fair judgement upon all, marking out the misdeeds…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">To protect the forest, I’ll lift the scale. Eternal judgement shall be delivered to them.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">To judge all the beasts that live in this forest…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

    <!-- Gee Apocalypse Bird, how come Binah lets you have SIX cards? -->
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_BigEye">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Big Eyes</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
At the start of the Scene, inflict 'Enchanted' to all enemies.
Enchanted enemies prioritize this librarian as a target, and deal +2-4 damage with attacks.
Gain 1-2 Power in clashes against Enchanted enemies, and recover 2-5 HP and Stagger Resist upon winning a clash.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The Big Bird’s eyes imprisoned light.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">The bright light is trapped.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Let’s be free before we have to face that fear…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">With just one simple act, I’ll give you a permanent and comfortable rest…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I have to be vigilant, watch out for any intruders.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_SmallPeak">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Small Beak</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add a 'Small Beak' page to hand: ‘Cost 0 - [On Play;] [Return to Hand] Take 5% of Max. HP as damage; restore 1 Light’.
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>And the Small Bird’s beak whispered, endlessly…</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I whisper, without cessation…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We are punished for our sins, but it’s clear that yet more will sprout from the roots of sin.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Thus, punishment must uproot sin…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I should punish them with my small but tough beak.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_LongArm">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Long Arms</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Take no damage from certain status ailments (Burn, Bleed, Fairy, Sin).</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The Long Bird’s arms concealed time.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I hide away time.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I condemn you, but you will still commit more sin without end…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">There will never be a day when this scale of justice does not tilt…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">My fair scale will determine who is more evil.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_Apocalypse">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>The Beast</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Activates when the selected librarian possesses all of the following Abnormality pages: 'Big Eyes', 'Small Beak', 'Long Arms'.
All dice of characters targeting or targeted by this character are unaffected by Power gain or loss, and their minimum and maximum values are lowered by 3.
At the end of the Scene, all other characters take 15 damage, and this character fully restores Light.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The day when Big Bird’s eyes that could see hundreds of kilometers away, Long Bird who could judge any sin, and Small Bird’s mouth that could devour everything united into one, darkness fell upon the forest.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I can’t let evil take all these precious things away.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If I could devour everything around me…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">We’ve joined forces to protect more people.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I have to hurry up and find them. I can’t have the beast destroy this place…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    <AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_Gate">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Guardians of the Forest</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
All librarians gain 1 Haste at the start of each Scene for the duration of the reception.
If all five librarians each have an Abnormality page, gain 1-2 Strength and Endurance in addition.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>That’s when the birds decided to become the guardians of the forest. They loved this forest more than anyone else did, so they wanted to protect the creatures living in the forest and keep the peace.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">To protect this place we love more than anyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We hope for a world where pitiful lives can live in comfort.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">We’re the only ones who can protect this place.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">We should become the guardians instead, and save lives.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
<AbnormalityCard ID="ApocalypseBird_Atk">
      <Abnormality>Apocalypse Bird</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Peace</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
When there is no 'Intruder' present, the first enemy the selected librarian attacks is marked as an 'Intruder'.(Excludes Mass Attacks)
All of the Intruder's attacks deal 2-4 less physical and Stagger damage; also, the Intruder takes 1-2 bonus damage from attacks.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The bird began to prowl the forest, looking for the beast. But there was nothing. There were no creatures, no sun and moon, and no beast. All that was left was just a bird and the Black Forest.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Those who endure the fear will attain peace…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Nothing will dare harm you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">When you reach the end, there will be no such thing as fear…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Peace and quiet have returned to the forest.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>

  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="Hokma">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodytree_Wing">
      <Abnormality>Burrowing Heaven</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Lean, Bloody Wings</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
On a deflect, deal half of the Block dice roll as physical damage to the opponent.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Once it recognizes that it lost your attention and focus… It will spread its wings. Like an angel, its wings will reach the skies and extend toward the ground, eventually blocking the sun out.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Basking in everyone’s gaze and attention… It will finally come to fruition and spread its wings.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">The one who spread their wings sacrificed everything they had, and yet…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">If we ever open our eyes again, will we get to see the fruit of our labor in that gaze?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Do not come here… There is nothing but a thorny tree; it’s no place for you to rest…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodytree_Gaze">
      <Abnormality>Burrowing Heaven</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Gaze of Others</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Deal +2-4 damage in a one-sided attack.
In a clash, deal 3-6 less damage with attacks, but Block dice gain 1-3 Power.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>That’s what a gaze is. Attention. An invisible string that connects us. Sole focus.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Just close your eyes. That’s right, you’re doing good…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">If you can’t see it, you can’t reach it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The desire for the unreachable will only grow bigger. And to pursue it… is to tread a path riddled with thorns.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Once it’s brought within your cognizance… It will return to this deep, dark underground…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodytree_Forcus">
      <Abnormality>Burrowing Heaven</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Attention and Focus</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Deal and take twice as much Stagger damage on a deflect.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Don’t look away, just keep your eyes on it. Contain it in your sight.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">You won’t bat an eye at this breathtaking sight.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Keep looking at it… Steadily… It’s alive, watching you in return, is it not?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Contain it in your sight…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">You watch me… and I watch you…</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="Clock_Time">
      <Abnormality>The Price of Silence</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Time</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
The player has 30 seconds to select Combat Pages before the combat phase begins each Scene.
Boost the Power of all dice of all librarians by 1-2.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Time flows as life does, and life goes as time does.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">That one doesn’t have enough time is a useless complaint.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Tomorrow may or may not come.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">You’ll be given more time than you have lost.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Time is given to everyone evenly, but fate makes it unfair.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Clock_Thirteen">
      <Abnormality>The Price of Silence</Abnormality>
      <CardName>The Thirteenth Toll</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Every 13th Combat Page the librarian plays gains 1-2 Power. (Excludes [On Play] pages)
The dice on the page also gain the following effect: ‘[On Hit] Deal bonus damage equal to (Dice value)% of target's Max HP’.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>I know of absolute solitude. I shared my silence, and now I take its price. Once the time comes and the original owner arrives, the price will be paid.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I heard that disastrous bell yet again.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">As the bell rang, a scream broke the silence at last…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">The bell tolls for the last time, in a moment that never seemed to come.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I gave out my silence, and now I take its price.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Clock_Kill">
      <Abnormality>The Price of Silence</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Silence</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add a 'Silence' page to the hand: ‘Cost 0 - [On Play] Take 15% of Max. HP as damage; all other characters lose 5 Speed’. 
Add an 'Amplify' page to the hand: ‘Cost 0 - [On Play] Take 10% of Max. HP as damage; Gain 5 Speed’.
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Rarely, I feel as if time has stopped. Fleeting moments of silence sometimes befall me.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Silence does not always bring peace.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">An instant of silence, as if time had stopped.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">When time stops, silence falls. In a way, they are one and the same.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Even when all has stopped, the soul will not perish.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="BlueStar_martyrdom">
      <Abnormality>Blue Star</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Martyr</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add a 'Martyr' page to hand: ‘Cost 0 - [On Play] For this Scene, deal 4-6 bonus Stagger damage with attacks but take 1-3 damage after a successful attack’.
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Let us meet again as stars.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Let’s relish eternal happiness at the end of this universe together.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Life cannot resist the instincts; we all go back to that place someday.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">We are not dying. We’re simply returning to where we belong.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="BlueStar_Atonement">
      <Abnormality>Blue Star</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Penance</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
If any character is Staggered at the start of the Scene, they take 3-7 damage, and all allies gain 1 Strength for the Scene. (Multiple Staggered characters do not give more Strength)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>Our Blue Star is the only sanctuary that accepts us. We will be cleansed of our sins there.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Let us completely take off this filthy husk and shine brightly.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">We shouldn’t let our anxiety fester inside us, busying ourselves trying to forget our wrongdoings by erasing them.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">We’ll all eventually go back to that place and cleanse ourselves of all sin there.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="BlueStar_Melody">
      <Abnormality>Blue Star</Abnormality>
      <CardName>A Nostalgic Sound</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
All allies deal +2-4 Stagger damage for this Scene. The effect of this page activates every 3 Scenes afterwards.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>The rise of a star is a brand new beginning. Don’t you hear the everlasting sound of the trumpet?</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Can you hear this sound? The nostalgic echo we’ve been eagerly searching for?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Aah… At last…! It’s calling for us at last!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">That call is guiding us to the only place that will accept us…!</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_Bless">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Baptism</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
Add a 'Baptism' page to hand: ‘Cost 2 - [On Play;] [Return to Hand] Target recovers 6 HP and gains 1 Endurance this Scene (Once per Scene)’.
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“I shall heal you, curing you of all disease and injury you possess.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">I am here to treat disease.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Place your trust in me. I am the only one who can help you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Why have you not treated that scar?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I shall heal you, curing you of all disease and injury you possess.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
        <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_Red">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Advent</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
For the duration of the reception, restore 1 additional Light at the start of the Scene.
If the selected librarian also has the Abnormality page 'Baptism', its effect is enhanced: ‘Target recovers 12 HP and gains 2 Endurance this Scene’.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“I am death and life. Darkness and light.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Ye who are drenched in sin. Rise and face me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I have not manifested myself in such a form to lay judgement.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I shall undo the restrictions that have imprisoned you in this place, and lead you to the paradise that welcomes everyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">I shall be with ye as I relieve you of the fear of horrifying death.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_Confess">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Confession</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรทุกคน]
Fully recover Stagger Resist, and purge all status ailments. (Also applies to Staggered librarians)
For the duration of the reception, take 2 less Stagger damage from attacks.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>To be willing to bear pain is half the atonement.</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">…</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">… …</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">… … …</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_Guard">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Sentinel</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
As long as there are other allies whom can be targeted, the selected librarian will not be targeted for attacks.
If this character is alive at the end of the reception, resolve an additional book for every guest defeated.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“Thou art His Son; thou art the King.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Ye who are full of blessings, rejoice. For I am with ye.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">I shall guide you to the paradise that welcomes everyone.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">I shall be with ye as I relieve you of the fear of horrifying death.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">We shall bask in the fortune of being together forever, and none shall leave.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_White">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Divine Power</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
While this character is alive, all other allies gain 2 Protection each Scene.
If this character has used WhiteNight's E.G.O page, allies also absorb instances of 3 or less damage.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“Be not frightened. I am thy savior and I shall be with thee.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Be at ease. No calamity shall be able to trouble you.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Ye will gain a body free of such corruption, so how could one deny that this is salvation.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Believe in me, and forever ye will be outside of the dark.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Ye will be revered, for I am divine.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
    
    <AbnormalityCard ID="WhiteNight_Apostle">
      <Abnormality>WhiteNight</Abnormality>
      <CardName>Apostles</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>[พันธมิตรเดี่ยว]
While this character is alive, all other allies deal +2-7 damage with attacks.
If the character has used 'Baptism' 12 or more times this reception, allies also gain +1 Power.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText>“Have not I chosen you twelve? Now rise, my servants. Rise and serve me.”</FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1">Pursue peace and holiness. Without these, ye shan’t look at me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="2">Those who endure until the end will be able to proceed.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="3">Accept my grace, and I shall bury your errors in the past.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue ID="4">Obey me and revel in the eternal life and mirth.</Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>

  
  <Sephirah SephirahType="None">
    <AbnormalityCard ID="Enemy_Fight">
      <Abnormality></Abnormality>
      <CardName>???</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>At the start of the Scene, gain 1 Strength.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText></FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1"></Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

    <AbnormalityCard ID="Enemy_Gloom">
      <Abnormality></Abnormality>
      <CardName>???</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>At the start of the Scene, gain 1 Feeble and 2 Endurance.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText></FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1"></Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

    <AbnormalityCard ID="Enemy_Friend">
      <Abnormality></Abnormality>
      <CardName>? ? ?</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>When another ally gets attacked, gain 1 Strength next Scene (Twice per Scene)</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText></FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1"></Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>

    <AbnormalityCard ID="Enemy_Bind">
      <Abnormality></Abnormality>
      <CardName>? ? ?</CardName>
      <AbilityDesc>At the start of the Scene, gain 1 Endurance.</AbilityDesc>
      <FlaborText></FlaborText>
      <Dialogues>
        <Dialogue ID="1"></Dialogue>
      </Dialogues>
    </AbnormalityCard>
  </Sephirah>
</AbnormalityCardsRoot>