<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<PassiveDesc ID="1001011">
<Name>แผลเป็น</Name>
<Desc>รับดาเมจจากการฟันน้อยลง 1-5 ดาเมจ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1001012">
<Name>Blood</Name>
<Desc>เสียความเร็ว 3 หน่วย เพิ่มค่าสูงสุดของลูกเต๋าป้องกัน +3.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1002021">
<Name>Aspiration</Name>
<Desc>หากไม่สามารถทำดาเมจได้ในฉากนี้ เสีย 4 HP</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 피노키오 : 거짓말쟁이 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="1003011">
<Name>สวมบทแทนตัว</Name>
<Desc>เลียนแบบเด็คของหัวหน้าบรรณารักษ์ ในแต่ละฉากจะฟื้นแสงจนเต็ม</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003012">
<Name>โกหกตดเหม็น</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ Page ที่จะมีการโกหกทุกๆ 2-3 ฉากโดยจะมีข้อมูลที่ผิดปกติ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003014">
<Name>คนโกหกจมูกจะยืด</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อปะทะกับ "อย่าโม้ครับน้อง!" ขณะที่โกหกอยู่ ลูกเต๋าทั้งหมดจะเสีย 4 พลัง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003015">
<Name>โป้ปด จับไม่ได้~~~</Name>
<Desc>ขณะที่โกหกอยู่ ลูกเต๋าทั้งหมดได้พลัง +4 หากไม่ได้ปะทะกับ "อย่าโม้ครับน้อง!"</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003016">
<Name>โกหกมันแย่ตรงไหน?</Name>
<Desc>หลังจากจับโกหกได้ พิน็อกคิโอทั้งหมดจะได้รับเปราะบาง
และตัดกำลัง 2 จำนวนในฉากถัดไป ความทนทาน
Stagger ทั้งหมดจะเปลี่ยนเป็น "อ่อนแอ"</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003018">
<Name>ลั้ลลัลลา~</Name>
<Desc>ถ้าจับโกหกไม่ได้ พิน็อกคิโอทั้งหมดจะได้รับกำลังและอึดทน 4 จำนวนในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 피노키오 : 호기심쟁이 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="1003021">
<Name>ฉันก็มี</Name>
<Desc>เลียนแบบเด็คของบรรณารักษ์คนแรก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003023">
<Name>บทเพลงย้อนกลับ</Name>
<Desc>ตราบที่ตัวละครนี้ยังมีชีวิตอยู่ ในแต่ละฉากจะสุ่มคอสของ Page ในมือใหม่ (ยกเว้น Page คอส 4)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 피노키오 : 따라쟁이 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="1003031">
<Name>เลียนแบบเสมือน</Name>
<Desc>เลียนแบบเด็คของบรรณารักษ์คนที่สอง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1003033">
<Name>บทเพลงแด่ทุกคน</Name>
<Desc>ราบที่ตัวละครนี้ยังมีชีวิตอยู่ เมื่อเริ่มฉาก พิน็อกคิโอทั้งหมดจะสุ่มว่าจะได้รับกำลังหรืออึดทน 2 จำนวนอย่างหนึ่ง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="101011">
<Name>เพลิงมรนัยสิ้น</Name>
<Desc>เสีย 50% จาก HP สูงสุดและ Staggered เมื่อพันธมิตรตายลง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="101012">
<Name>ธุลี</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อ Staggered จะเสียแสงทั้งหมด</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="102011">
<Name>Affection</Name>
<Desc>ลดคอสของ 'Nostalgic Embrace of the Old Days' ลง 1 หลังจากเข้าร่วมการปะทะ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="201011">
<Name>โทสะ</Name>
<Desc>การโจมตีทำดาเมจ Stagger สองเท่า</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="201012">
<Name>หวาดกลัว</Name>
<Desc>หากตัวละครมีสถานะผิดปกติอยู่ ลูกเต๋าทั้งหมดจะเสียพลัง -4</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="202011">
<Name>รูปแบบทำซ้ำ - Recognition</Name>
<Desc>หลังจากทำดาเมจได้ถึง 10 ดาเมจหรือมากกว่าในฉากเดียว ฟื้นแสง 1</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="301011">
<Name>สีหน้า</Name>
<Desc>ลูกเต๋าจะได้หรือเสียพลังต่างกันไป ขึ้นอยู่กับหน้าในขณะนั้น</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="302021">
<Name>ถูกดึงดูด</Name>
<Desc>เพ่งเป้าไปยังคนที่มีเลือดไหลก่อน</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="401011">
<Name>ไม่สามารถหยั่งถึง</Name>
<Desc>ทำดาเมจ Stagger สองเท่าจากทุกแหล่ง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="402011">
<Name>ก้อนกรวด</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉากฟื้นฟู HP 10% จะไม่ทำงาน หาก HP เหลือ 1</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="402012">
<Name>อย่าทิ้งฉันไป~</Name>
<Desc>HP จะไม่ลดไปต่ำกว่า 1; จะถูก Staggered เมื่อรับดาเมจถึงตาย
หลังจากนั้น 2 ฉาก ฟื้นฟู HP ให้เท่า HP ปัจจุบันของพันธมิตร
ถ้าพันธมิตรทั้งหมดเหลือ HP 1 เมื่อเริ่มฉากจะตาย</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="402013">
<Name>น้ำตาแห่งกรแยกจาก</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ถ้ามีพันธมิตรเหลือ HP 1 (รวมถึงตัวเอง) ตัวละครทั้งหมดเสีย HP 10% จาก HP สูงสุด</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 요정 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="103011">
<Name>ท้องแน่นครู่หนึ่ง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก เมื่อพันธมิตรทีมีสถานะ Prepared Meat เหลือ 1 HP จะกินมันแล้วรับเปราะบาง อ่อนแรง และตัดกำลัง 10 จำนวนในฉากนั้น</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 요정 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="103012">
<Name>กระหายคลั่ง</Name>
<Desc>หาก HP ลดลงเหลือ 25% หรือต่ำกว่า ฆ่าพันธมิตรทั้งหมด และจะได้รับกำลัง 30 จำนวนหากไม่มีพันธมิตรเหลืออยู่ในขณะนั้น</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 요정 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="103021">
<Name>หิวโหย</Name>
<Desc>ในแต่ละฉาก เสีย 6 HP และจะได้รับกำลัง 2 จำนวนถ้า HP เหลือ 50% หรือต่ำกว่า</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 요정 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="103022">
<Name>ปกปักษ์</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ฟื้นฟู 10 HP และ HP จะไม่ลดไปต่ำกว่า 1 จนกว่าราชินีจะตาย</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 거미봉오리 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="303011">
<Name>ล่าหัว</Name>
<Desc>เล็งเป้าหมายคนที่ฆ่าพันธมิตร</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="303012">
<Name>ได้เวลาออกล่า</Name>
<Desc>หลังจากพันธมิตรตาย จะเริ่มตอบโต้เป็นเวลาสองเทิร์น</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 거미봉오리 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="303021">
<Name>ถึงเวลามื้อเย็น!</Name>
<Desc>เล็งเป้าหมายที่มีสถานะ "Cocoon"</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 포큐버스 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="403011">
<Name>ขวากหนามมอบสุนทรี</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อถูกโจมตี มอบเหรียญอารมณ์บวก 2 แต้ม</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 포큐버스 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="403012">
<Name>กระพริกกระพรือ</Name>
<Desc>ไม่รับดาเมจจากการโจมตีระยะไกล</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="403013">
<Name>ความสุขที่เกินต้าน</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มต้นในแต่ละฉาก แต่ละตัวละครจะฟื้น 1 แสงต่อจำนวน "Pleasure" ในมือ
เมื่อโจมตี หากเป้าหมาายมี "Pleasure" 3 ใบ ทำดาเมจ 20 ดาเมจ
และสลาย Page ดังกล่าว</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 노래하는 기계 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="203011">
<Name>เครื่องจักร์ที่ร้องเพลงได้</Name>
<Desc>ไม่สามารถถูกเลือกเป้าได้ ไม่มีการโจมตี ไม่รับดาเมจ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="203012">
<Name>การแสดง</Name>
<Desc>ฉากหลังจาก "ฉันต้องได้ฟังเพลงบรรเลงนั้น!!!" ทำงาน
เล่นเพลงโดยใช้ตัวละครที่ยู่ในนั้น
ตัวละครดังกล่าวได้รับดาเมจ 30% ของ HP สูงสุด
และถูกเอาออกจากการต่อสู้ในฉากนั้น
ขณะที่ดนตรีบรรเลงอยู่ ทุกตัวละครได้รับกำลัง 5 จำนวน
และความต้านทาน Stagger เปลี่ยนเป็น "ร้ายแรง"</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="203021">
<Name>ฉันต้องได้ฟังเพลงบรรเลงนั้น!!!</Name>
<Desc>เริ่มทำงานในฉากที่สาม; ทุกๆ สี่ฉาก
ได้รับลูกเต๋าความเร็วเพิ่ม และใช้ Combat Pages ชุดใหม่
หาก Staggered โดยเอฟเฟคนี้ทำงาน จะถูกยัดเข้าเครื่องจักร
ในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 증오의 여왕 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="501011">
<Name>เปลี่ยนผันที่เงาร้าย</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อหลอดฮิลทีเรียเต็ม จะแปลงร่าง
หลอดฮิสทีเรียจะเพิ่มเมื่อแพ้การปะทะหรือถูกโจมตีโดยตัวละครที่ถูกทำเครื่องหมาย
และจะลดลงเมื่อชนะการปะทะหรือโจมตีตัวละครที่ถูกทำเครื่องหมาย
หลอดฮิสทีเรียจะเปลี่ยนเป็นสีชมพูตามฉากหลัง
เมื่อจบฉาก ฟื้นฟูแสงทั้งหมดและจั่ว 2 Page</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="501012">
<Name>ในนามของความเกลียดชัง</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ Page ที่จะมอบ "ถูกทำเครื่องหมาย" ใส่เป้าหมายทุกๆ 2 ฉาก
ความทนทานของตัวละครดังกล่าวจะเปลี่ยนเป็น "อ่อนแอ" และจะถูกเล็งโดย
Abnormality เป็นเป้าหมายหลัก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="501013">
<Name>Arcana Slave</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ Page โจมตีหมู่ในทุกๆ 4 ฉาก หาก Abnormality ใช้ Page ในขณะที่แปลงร่าง
มันจะ Staggered ในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 절망의 기사 본체-->
<PassiveDesc ID="502011">
<Name>ภักดีพิทักษ์ตน</Name>
<Desc>ไม่สามารถถูกเลือกเป้าได้ ไม่มีการโจมตี</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502012">
<Name>ความโศกเศร้า</Name>
<Desc>สุ่มมอบน้ำตาให้กับดาบเล่มหนึ่งในทุกๆ 3 ฉาก
หากตัวละคร Staggered จะเริ่มทำงานในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502013">
<Name>ความสิ้นหวัง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อดาบที่มีน้ำตาได้รับดาเมจถึงตาย
จะตกสู่ความสิ้นหวังในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502014">
<Name>การอวยพรแห่งความสิ้นหวัง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อ Abnormality ตกสู่ความสิ้นหวัง
ดาบทั้งหมดจะฟื้น HP และ Stagger Resist ทังหมด
และใช้ Combat Pages พิเศษ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502015">
<Name>หัวใจแตกสลาย</Name>
<Desc>หากดาบทั้งหมดแทง Abnormality ในสถานะสิ้นหวัง
จะ Staggered และสามารถถูกโจมตีได้ในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 절망의 기사 칼 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="502021">
<Name>น้ำตา</Name>
<Desc>ได้รับลูกเต๋าความเร็วเพิ่ม ใช้ Pages พิเศษ
และจะเปลี่ยนค่าความทนทานเมื่อมีสถานะน้ำตา</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502022">
<Name>พักผ่อน</Name>
<Desc>จะหมดสภาพต่อสู้เมื่อรับดาเมจถึงตาย ฟื้นกลับมาเมื่อครบสองฉาก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="502023">
<Name>ดาบทะลวงความสิ้นหวัง</Name>
<Desc>หากไม่สามารถทำดาเมจได้ในขณะที่อยู่ในสถานะสิ้นหวัง
ดาบจะแทงใส่ Knight of Despair และทำดาเมจใส่เธอ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 여왕벌 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="104011">
<Name>สปอร์</Name>
<Desc>หากถูกโจมตี มอบ 1 สปอร์ใส่บรรณารักษ์ทั้งหมดเมื่อเริ่มฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="104012">
<Name>ชูชันสร้างแรงงาน</Name>
<Desc>หากมี Worker Bees 2 ตัวหรือน้อยกว่า
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก มอบ 2 สปอร์ใส่บรรณารักษ์ทั้งหมด</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="104013">
<Name>แปลงสภาพ</Name>
<Desc>หากบรรณารักษ์ตายขณะติดสถานะสปอร์
เสก Worker Bee ในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="104014">
<Name>ฟีโรโมน</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ Pages เพิ่มการโจมตีและความภักดีของ Worker Bees
ในทุกๆ 3 ฉาก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 일벌-->
<PassiveDesc ID="104021">
<Name>ความภักดี</Name>
<Desc>เล็งเป้าหมายที่โจมตี Queen Bee เป็นคนสุดท้ายในฉากที่แล้ว</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="104022">
<Name>ความกล้าสู่การเผชิญความตาย</Name>
<Desc>หาก Queen Bee เหลือ HP 20% หรือต่ำกว่า จะโจมตี Queen Bee</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 붉은 두건의 용병 : 용병-->
<PassiveDesc ID="601011">
<Name>จุดจบของฝันร้าย</Name>
<Desc>การต่อสู้จะจบลงหากหนูน้อยหมวกแดงฆ่าหมาป่าได้;
การต่อสู้จะแพ้ทันทีหากหนูน้อยหมวกแดงตายก่อนหมาป่า</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="601012">
<Name>ไม่รีรอ</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ "จู่โจมอย่างไม่ลังเล" ในทุกๆ 2-3 ฉาก เล็งทุกเป้าหมาย</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="601013">
<Name>เพลิงรักแรงแค้น</Name>
<Desc>หากหลอดความโกรธเต็ม เข้าสถานะโกรธ
หลอดความโกรธจะเพิ่มเมื่อถูกหมาป่าโจมตี
และลดลงเมื่อโจมตีหมาป่า
หน้าจอจะเปลี่ยนเป็นสีแสงเมื่อหลอดความโกรธเพิ่มขึ้น

โกรธแค้น: เป็นระยะเวลา 2 ฉาก
ได้รับกำลัง +2 จำนวนในแต่ละฉาก ใช้ Pages โจมตีหมู่</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="601014">
<Name>เก็บกดคลั่งแค้น</Name>
<Desc>ถ้าบรรณารักษ์เป็นผู้ฆ่าหมาป่า Abnormality จะเข้าสู่สภาวะ "เก็บกดคลั่งแค้น"
และได้รับ HP สูงสุดและ Stagger Resist เพิ่มเติม
จากนั้น ฟื้นฟู HP 50% และ Stagger Resist ทั้งหมด
เก็บกดคลั่งแค้น: คงอยู่ถาวร ได้รับกำลังและว่องไว +5 จำนวนในแต่ละฉาก ใช้ Pages โจมตีหมู่</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 붉은 두건의 용병 : 늑대 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="601021">
<Name>หมาป่าเห่าหอน</Name>
<Desc>ใช้ "เห่าหอน" ในทุกๆ 3~4 ฉาก เล็งทุกเป้าหมาย</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="601022">
<Name>ฝันร้ายคำรามก้อง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อ HP ลดลงเหลือ 50% หรือต่ำกว่า ได้รับลูกเต๋าความเร็วเพิ่ม
และจะใช้เห่าหอนทุกฉาก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 허수아비 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="701011">
<Name>เก็บเกี่ยว</Name>
<Desc>ทุกๆ 3 ฉาก ได้รับลูกเต๋าความเร็วเพิ่มและใช้ "เก็บเกี่ยวปัญญา"
โดยจะดูดซับเอา Combat Page และฟื้นฟู HP เมื่อโจมตี 
หากเป้าหมายไม่เหลือ Combat Pages ให้ดูดซับ
ทำดาเมจโบนัส (5~20) ดาเมจแทน</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="701012">
<Name>ผู้มีปัญญาจักสงบนิ่ง</Name>
<Desc>หาก "เก็บเกี่ยวปัญญา" ปะทะกับ "ปัญญา" 
Abnormality จะได้รับดาเมจ Stagger 20 ดาเมจหลังการปะทะ
และได้รับอ่อนแรงและพันธนา 3 จำนวนในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="701013">
<Name>ความมุมานะของสมอง</Name>
<Desc>หลังจากดูดซับ Page ที่ไม่ใช่ "ปัญญา" ด้วย "เก็บเกี่ยวปัญญา"
ได้รับกำลังและอึดทนเท่ากับจำนวน Page ที่ดูดซับมา
และใช้หนึ่งใน Page ที่ดูดซับมา</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="701014">
<Name>เจาะสมองแล้วดูดจ๊วบๆ</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก บรรณารักษ์ทั้งหมดที่ไม่มี Page จะ Staggered</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 나무꾼 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="702011">
<Name>ป่าทึบ</Name>
<Desc>ถ้าตัวละครนี้มี Warm Heart
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก บรรณารักษ์ทั้งหมดจะฟื้นแสงจนเต็ม</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="702012">
<Name>ยังไม่ได้ ยังไม่พอ</Name>
<Desc>ในแต่ละฉาก เล็งเป้าไปยังบรรณารักษ์ที่มีแสงมากที่สุด</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="702013">
<Name>เอาหัวใจนั้นมา</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อโจมตี ลูกเต๋าทั้งหมดจะได้รับพลังตามจำนวนแสงที่เป้าหมายมี</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="702014">
<Name>นาฬิกาใจ</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อฆ่าเป้าหมายสำเร็จ ฟื้นฟู HP 20%
และได้รับ Warm Heart 3 จำนวน</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="702015">
<Name>หัวใจฉันไม่อยู่ตรงนี้ มันว่างเปล่า</Name>
<Desc>ถ้าตัวละครนี้ไม่มี Warm Heart
เมื่อเริ่มฉากจะ Staggered.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="702021">
<Name>ผู้ครองใจเธอ คือฉันนี่เอง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ถ้า Warm Heart(s) เหลืออยู่ 0
Woodsman จะสับใส่ตัวละครนี้</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 죽나장 -->
<PassiveDesc ID="204011">
<Name>หัตถ์แห่งความพ้นภัย</Name>
<Desc>เล็งเป้าหมายที่ HP น้อยที่สุด
เล็งเป้าหมายที่ถูกผนึกลูกเต๋าเป็นพิเศษ</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="204012">
<Name>เจียมตัวสงบนิ่ง</Name>
<Desc>หากลูกเต๋าทั้งหมดถูกผนึกโดยเอฟเฟคของ Page ของ Abnormality ตัวนี้
พวกเขาทั้งหมดจะ Staggered</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="204013">
<Name>คร่ำครวญ</Name>
<Desc>ถ้ามีศัตรูที่ Staggered อยู่
เมื่อเริ่มฉาก ใช้ Page โจมตีหมู่</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!-- 죽나장 나비-->
<PassiveDesc ID="204021">
<Name>กระพรือไปอย่างไร้ประโยชน์</Name>
<Desc>เล็งเป้าหมายที่มี HP ต่ำที่สุด;
จะถูกปราบลงเมื่อ Funeral of the Dead Butterflies ถูกปราบลง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="602011">
<Name>บทบาทของหมาป่า</Name>
<Desc>ทุกๆ 2 ฉาก ใช้ Combat Page ที่จะกลืนเป้าหมายเมื่อโจมตี
เป้าหมายที่ถูกกลืนจะถูกเอาออกจากการต่อสู้ในฉากถัดไป</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="602012">
<Name>ช่วงคืนกวีแห่งความเที่ยงธรรม</Name>
<Desc>หลังจากกลืนบรรณารักษ์แล้ว ในฉากถัดไป ความทนทาน Stagger ทั้งหมดเปลี่ยนเป็น "ร้ายแรง"
หากหมาป่า Staggered ในฉากนั้น คายบรรณารักษ์ออกมา
บรรณารักษ์จะเสีย HP 25% จากทั้งหมดเมื่อถูกคายและ Staggered ด้วย</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="602013">
<Name>ชะตาชี้กำหนดให้เป็นหมาป่าใหญ่และชั่วร้าย</Name>
<Desc>หากหมาป่าไม่ถูก Staggered หลังจากกลืนบรรณารักษ์
บรรณารักษ์คนนั้นจะถูกฆ่า และหมาป่าจะแปรงร่าง
หากหมาป่าเหลือ HP 50% หรือต่ำกว่า ก็จะแปรงร่างเมื่อเริ่มฉากเช่นกัน
HP จะไม่ลดไปต่ำกว่า 30% จนกว่าจะแปรงร่าง</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="602021">
<Name>แปรงร่าง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อแปรงร่าง Stagger Resist เพิ่มขึ้นและฟื้นฟูจนเต็ม</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="602022">
<Name>สู่เงามืด</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อแอบนอร์มาลิตี้เสีย HP 25% หรือมากกว่า นับจากตอนแปรงร่าง
จะได้รับสถานะ "Skulking in the Shadows" เป็นเวลา 2 ฉาก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="602023">
<Name>เงาคืบคลาน</Name>
<Desc>ขณะที่แอบนอร์มาลิตี้มีสถานะ "Skulking in the Shadows"
บรรณารักษ์คนอื่นที่ไม่ได้ถูกเล็งโดยมัน จะเล็งใส่แอบนอร์มาลิตี้ไม่ได้</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="602024">
<Name>อ่อนล้า</Name>
<Desc>หลังจาก "Skulking in the Shadows" หมดลง ความทนทาน Stagger ทั้งหมดเปลี่ยนเป็น "ร้ายแรง" หนึ่งฉาก</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="503010">
<Name>อัมพันสีเหลืองทอง</Name>
<Desc>Does not act. If HP reaches 0 before the end of the Scene, awakens as a Magical Girl. Otherwise, awakens as the King of Greed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503011">
<Name>ความปราถนาที่ปลายทาง</Name>
<Desc>If HP falls to 50% or lower, transform into the King of Greed next Scene. HP does not go below 50% before transformation.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503012">
<Name>ถนนสีทองคำ</Name>
<Desc>Every 3 Scenes, creates Brilliant Bliss and becomes untargetable, but does not act. The following Scene, uses a special Combat Page against all librarians.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503013">
<Name>ผู้หลงตัวเอง</Name>
<Desc>If three or fewer librarians manage to negate the attack of the special Combat Page, gain 3 Strength and Haste next Scene. (If two or less librarians are alive, one or no librarians negating the page will activate this effect)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503014">
<Name>Momentary Bliss</Name>
<Desc>If all librarians successfully negate the attack of the special Combat Page, the Abnormality becomes Staggered next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503021">
<Name>The King of Greed</Name>
<Desc>Uses a different set of Combat Pages. On a successful hit, deal bonus damage equal to stacks of Bleed on the target.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503022">
<Name>หนทางสู่ราชา</Name>
<Desc>Every 3 Scenes, creates Brilliant Bliss and becomes untargetable, but does not act. The following Scene, uses two special Combat pages against a single target.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503023">
<Name>Voracity</Name>
<Desc>If a librarian fails to negate any one of the special Combat Page's attacks, deal 15 damage to all librarians and recover 25 HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503024">
<Name>A Moment’s Bliss</Name>
<Desc>If a librarian successfully negates all attacks of the special Combat Page, the Abnormality becomes Staggered next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="503031">
<Name>Brilliant Bliss</Name>
<Desc>Exists for one Scene. Gives special Combat Pages to the librarian that defeats it.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="304011">
<Name>I’ll Give You a Gift!</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes the target with the least amount of 'Gifts' in hand.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304012">
<Name>Will You Play With Me?</Name>
<Desc>Block dice lose Power by 4x the number of 'Gifts' in the opponent's hand.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304013">
<Name>Being Lonely is Sad</Name>
<Desc>If all other allies have died, all resistances change to "ร้ายแรง".</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304021">
<Name>Gi...ft...</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes the target with the most amount of 'Gifts' in hand.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304022">
<Name>BOOM!</Name>
<Desc>On the third Scene, uses a powerful Combat Page that deals significant damage and gives three copies of 'Gift' to its target before causing the user to self-destruct. The character dies after using that page.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304023">
<Name>Here Comes a Surprise Present</Name>
<Desc>If this character dies, a Wee Witch’s Friend is spawned next Scene. If the character is killed before it can self-destruct using the special Combat Page, the Friend is spawned with 80% HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304031">
<Name>Gi...ft...</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes the target with the most amount of 'Gifts' in hand.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="304032">
<Name>Gimme That Gift!</Name>
<Desc>Offensive dice gain Power equal to the number of 'Gifts' in the target's hand.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="404015">
<Name>Doll Fashioned from Earth</Name>
<Desc>Takes no damage from Burn or Bleed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404012">
<Name>Blossoming Fragrance</Name>
<Desc>This character's attacks only deal Stagger damage to librarians. If a librarian becomes Staggered, they are instantly killed, and 'One Who Emerged from the Earth' is spawned next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404011">
<Name>Breathless Atonement</Name>
<Desc>The Abnormality only takes damage from the librarian with the 'Laurel Wreath' status.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404013">
<Name>Unwithering Flower</Name>
<Desc>Starting from Scene 2, a petal blooms behind the Abnormality at the start of each Scene. If three petals have accumulated at the start of a Scene, remove all of them and use a Mass Attack page.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404014">
<Name>Tears of Petals</Name>
<Desc>Upon becoming Staggered, lose 40 HP and remove all petals at the start of the next Scene. In addition, all librarians recover 50% of their max Stagger Resist.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404021">
<Name>To the Earth Whence I Come…</Name>
<Desc>This character dies upon becoming Staggered.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404023">
<Name>Doll Fashioned from Earth</Name>
<Desc>Takes no damage from Burn or Bleed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="404022">
<Name>Blossoming Fragrance</Name>
<Desc>This character's attacks only deal Stagger damage to librarians. If a librarian becomes Staggered, they are instantly killed, and 'One Who Emerged from the Earth' is spawned next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="801011">
<Name>Watchful Eyes</Name>
<Desc>Big Bird's targets cannot be redirected by librarians.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="801012">
<Name>A Lamp that Burns Forever</Name>
<Desc>Uses 'Dazzle' on the first Scene and every 3 Scenes after, which inflicts 'Enchanted' on a librarian. When a librarian is Enchanted, a copy of 'Birdcage' is added to the hands of all librarians who aren't Enchanted.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="801021">
<Name>Sleepy Eyes</Name>
<Desc>Gives a special Combat Page that can Stagger Big Bird to the librarian that defeats this character.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="801022">
<Name>Follower</Name>
<Desc>Does not target Enchanted librarians.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="901011">
<Name>Sole Focus</Name>
<Desc>Becomes active if no Thorns are awake. Uses a Mass Attack page on the same Scene it became active.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901012">
<Name>Wings for an Old God</Name>
<Desc>While this character is active, all librarians are inflicted with 10 Feeble เมื่อเริ่มฉาก.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901013">
<Name>In Your Sight</Name>
<Desc>Takes twice as much Stagger damage from deflects.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901014">
<Name>Into Cognizance</Name>
<Desc>If this character remains active for 3 Scenes, a Heaven’s Thorn will be spawned next Scene and every 3 Scenes after.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901021">
<Name>Don’t Look Away</Name>
<Desc>If a librarian engages in combat against another character, all other librarians take damage equal to 40% of their Max HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901022">
<Name>Invisible String of Connection</Name>
<Desc>After engaging in combat with a librarian, inflict them with Feeble next Scene; the amount is equal to the number of Combat Pages the librarian has used against this character during the battle.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="901023">
<Name>In Your Sight</Name>
<Desc>Takes twice as much Stagger damage from deflects.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="1004011">
<Name>Biting Wind</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, all librarians lose HP equal to 5% of their Max HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1004012">
<Name>Reticent Frigidity</Name>
<Desc>Takes no damage from attacks until all Prisons of Ice are destroyed. Takes no damage from Burn or Bleed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1004013">
<Name>Frost Column</Name>
<Desc>Gains Speed dice and Light capacity based on the number of destroyed Prisons of Ice. If two or more Prisons have been destroyed, a melee Mass Attack page is added to this character's deck.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1004014">
<Name>Those who know the Cruelty of Winter and the Aroma of Roses</Name>
<Desc>After all Prisons of Ice have been destroyed, all librarians recover 50% of their Max HP. The Snow Queen will use a Mass Attack page the same Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1004021">
<Name>Kai and Gerda</Name>
<Desc>If this character's HP drops to 0, an imprisoned librarian is freed next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="603011">
<Name>In Search of Corpses</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes using 'Devour' on allies. Recovers 30% of current HP upon defeating an ally.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603012">
<Name>Melted Corpses</Name>
<Desc>Each time the Abnormality loses more than 25% of the Max. HP (62/87/112), 'Melting Corpses' is spawned at the start of the next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603111">
<Name>Dividing</Name>
<Desc>Divides into corpses when HP drops to 0. If all corpses are defeated within 3 Scenes, the battle is won. Otherwise, the Abnormality revives as Stage 1. (Upon revival, it will recover HP by the sum of the HP all remaining Melting Corpses had.)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603112">
<Name>Growing Mass</Name>
<Desc>Transforms to Stage 2 upon fully recovering HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603211">
<Name>Divisible Yet Addable</Name>
<Desc>Transforms back to Stage 1 when HP drops to 0. Transforms to Stage 3 upon fully recovering HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603212">
<Name>Terrifying Laughter</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, gain 1 Strength. Uses 'Horrid Screech' every 2 Scenes.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603311">
<Name>Division</Name>
<Desc>Transforms back to Stage 2 when HP drops to 0.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603312">
<Name>Putrid Vomit</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, gain 2 Strength. Uses 'Vomit' every 2 Scenes.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="603021">
<Name>Rot</Name>
<Desc>Upon taking a hit, deal 8 damage to the librarian that attacked it and inflict 1 Fragile to them.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="703021">
<Name>Let’s Go Together…</Name>
<Desc>On the first Scene of the battle, spawns the 'Home', and uses a Mass Attack Page that applies the status 'Yellow Brick Road' to its targets.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="703022">
<Name>Friends! Let’s Go Home~!</Name>
<Desc>On the second Scene, uses the Combat Page 'Friends! Let’s Go Home~!' targeting the 'Home' and the librarians with 'Yellow Brick Road'. 
If the Combat Page hits 'Home', the battle is lost.
The attack on the 'Home' is canceled if all librarians with 'Yellow Brick Road' win the clash against 'Friends! Let’s Go Home~!'.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="703023">
<Name>You… Gosh Darned Wizard…!</Name>
<Desc>After the Abnormality's attack towards 'Home' has been canceled two times, uses a Mass Attack ("You… Wicked Wizard!") the following Scene. If any librarian is hit by the attack, the 'Home' is spawned next Scene, and repeats the previous behavior.
If no librarian is damaged by the attack, the Abnormality becomes Staggered next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="703031">
<Name>Courageous</Name>
<Desc>Is immune to all types of damage until 'The Road Home' dies.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="703032">
<Name>Cowardly</Name>
<Desc>Once 'The Road Home' dies, all resistances change to "ร้ายแรง", and Max HP is reduced. The number of Speed dice and Combat Pages also change.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="504011">
<Name>Today’s Play</Name>
<Desc>Only the Servant of Wrath can defeat the Hermit. The Abnormality battle is concluded when the Hermit is defeated.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504012">
<Name>Blind Rage</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes attacking the Hermit’s Staves. If no Hermit’s Staff is present, attacks the Hermit.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504013">
<Name>Sinners of the Otherworlds!</Name>
<Desc>While one or more Hermit's Staves are present, after taking 30 total damage, uses a Mass Attack page, 'EMBODIMENTS OF EVIL!!!!' on the following Scene. The total damage counter is reset afterwards.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504014">
<Name>Boiling Anger</Name>
<Desc>When the Abnormality starts attacking the Hermit, uses a Mass Attack page, 'EMBODIMENTS OF EVIL!!!!'. The page is used every 2 Scenes after.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504021">
<Name>The Exploited</Name>
<Desc>HP does not fall below 30 from a librarian's attacks. If the character's HP is at 30 or lower at the end of a Scene, recovers 50% of Max HP next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504022">
<Name>Dear Companion</Name>
<Desc>Gains +5 Power when clashing against the Servant of Wrath. Takes no damage from Burn, Bleed, or Erosion.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504023">
<Name>Visitor from Another World</Name>
<Desc>While one or more Hermit’s Staves are present, uses a Mass Attack page every 2 Scenes.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504024">
<Name>When Two Realms Meet</Name>
<Desc>Changes behavior when all Hermit’s Staves are defeated. On the first Scene of the new cycle, attacks the Servant of Wrath.
After attacking the Servant of Wrath again on the second Scene, uses a Mass Attack page that summons more Hermit’s Staves.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="504031">
<Name>Hermit’s Staff</Name>
<Desc>Attacks the Servant of Wrath.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="902011">
<Name>Time Flowing</Name>
<Desc>Cannot be targeted. Every Scene, the player is given 30 seconds to select Combat Pages before the combat phase starts. เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, give other allies one of the following: 'Gain +3 Power in a clash' or 'Gain +3 Power in a one-sided attack'.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="902012">
<Name>Time Cumulating</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, spawns a 'Remnant of Time'. If 4 Remnants of Time are already present, the one with the lowest HP is replaced and all librarians take damage equal to its HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="902013">
<Name>Time Unstopping</Name>
<Desc>If 12 Remnants of Time are defeated within 12 Scenes, becomes Staggered the following Scene. If fewer than 12 Remnants of Time were defeated by the end of the 12th Scene, uses a Mass Attack page on the thirteenth (13th) Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="902014">
<Name>The Price of Silence</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, add a copy of 'Silence' to the hands of all librarians.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="902021">
<Name>Your Betiding</Name>
<Desc>Copies the Speed dice number, Speed values, and resistances of a librarian. Combat Pages played by said librarian this Scene will be played by this character next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>


<PassiveDesc ID="802011">
<Name>Misdeeds Not Allowed!</Name>
<Desc>Gains +50 Power when clashing against Offensive dice.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="802012">
<Name>Punishment!</Name>
<Desc>If the Abnormality took damage this Scene, uses the Combat Page 'Punishment!' against the character that attacked it last next Scene. (Cannot be redirected)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="802013">
<Name>Rattling Cage</Name>
<Desc>When 'Punishment!' clashes against 'Forest Keeper’s Lock', a chain on the birdcage breaks.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="802021">
<Name>Forest Keeper</Name>
<Desc>Prioritizes targeting Staggered characters. This character's Offensive dice gain +2 Power against targets with slower Speed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="802022">
<Name>Stolen Lock</Name>
<Desc>Gives a special Combat Page, 'Forest Keeper’s Lock', to the librarian that defeats this character.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="803011">
<Name>Unjust Scale</Name>
<Desc>Starting with Scene 1, all characters excluding Judgement Bird gain 1 Sin เมื่อเริ่มฉาก. Sin can be transferred to an ally by attacking and damaging them. (Once per page)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803012">
<Name>The Weight of Sin</Name>
<Desc>All dice gain Power equal to the amount of Sin the target has.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803013">
<Name>Judgement</Name>
<Desc>If a character has 5 or more Sin เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, uses the special Combat Page ‘Judgement’ on them.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803014">
<Name>Ceaseless Judgement</Name>
<Desc>If three or more characters have 3+ Sin เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, uses a Mass attack page: ‘Ceaseless Judgement’.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803015">
<Name>Overflowing Misdeeds</Name>
<Desc>After using 'Judgement' or 'Ceaseless Judgement', lose 25% of Max. Stagger Resist.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803021">
<Name>I’m Scared! I’m Scared!</Name>
<Desc>If this character's attack hits, transfer 1 Sin to the target. (Once per page)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="803022">
<Name>Piercing Shriek</Name>
<Desc>After taking an attack, uses the Combat Page 'Piercing Shriek' next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>


<PassiveDesc ID="604011">
<Name>Fear of Water</Name>
<Desc>If the character has less than 5 Blood, gain Strength proportional to the amount of Blood missing. (Up to 3)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604012">
<Name>Thirst</Name>
<Desc>If the character has 2 or less Blood, uses a special Combat Page. (Has a 2 Scene cooldown.)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604013">
<Name>Banquet of Blood</Name>
<Desc>If the character has 5 or more Blood, uses a Mass Attack page: 'Banquet of Blood'. (Has a 3 Scene cooldown.)
If the character did not use the page for the first 4 Scenes of the battle, it will be used on the 5th Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604014">
<Name>Shapeshifting</Name>
<Desc>If HP falls to 50% or lower, shapeshift next Scene. HP does not go below 50% before this.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604031">
<Name>Fear of Water</Name>
<Desc>If the character has less than 5 Blood, gain Strength proportional to the amount of Blood missing. (Up to 3)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604032">
<Name>Flowing Blood</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, lose 1 Blood.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604033">
<Name>Unbearable Drought</Name>
<Desc>If the character has 2 or less Blood, uses a special Combat Page. (Has a 2 Scene cooldown.)</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604034">
<Name>Lust for Blood</Name>
<Desc>If the character has 0 Blood, uses a Mass Attack page: 'Lust for Blood'. (Has a 3 Scene cooldown.)
If the character did not use the page for 3 Scenes after shapeshifting, it will be used on the 4th Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="604021">
<Name>Fear of Water</Name>
<Desc>If the character has 1 or less Blood, gain 2 Strength.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!-- 오즈마-->
 <PassiveDesc ID="704011">
 <Name>Revive</Name>
 <Desc>On the first Scene, uses Combat Pages that awaken all Jacks and inflict Oblivion on a librarian. Afterwards, follows a unique pattern of behavior that cycles every 4 Scenes.</Desc>
 </PassiveDesc>
 <PassiveDesc ID="704012">
<Name>Agony of the Deprived</Name>
<Desc>After a librarian with Oblivion is restored from the status, all resistances of this character change to "ร้ายแรง" at the start of the next Scene, and uses a Mass Attack page. Repeats the pattern afterwards.</Desc>
 </PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704013">
<Name>Grief of the Deprived</Name>
<Desc>After 2 cycles have passed, all Stagger damage resistances of this character change to "ร้ายแรง" at the start of the next Scene, and uses an extremely powerful Mass Attack page.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!--잭-->
<PassiveDesc ID="704021">
<Name>พลังที่ขโมยมา</Name>
<Desc>Uses the Combat Pages of the librarian with Oblivion.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704022">
<Name>อันไหนล่ะของจริง</Name>
<Desc>Only one of the Jacks that awaken is real; the rest are fakes.
Whenever a librarian with Oblivion hits the real Jack, it gives back a Combat Page that was stolen from them.
The screen blinks when the real Jack is hit.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
 <PassiveDesc ID="704023">
<Name>ขโมย หรือจะถูกขโมย</Name>
<Desc>After the librarian with Oblivion hits the real Jack 9 times, all Jacks die.
If the condition isn't fulfilled within 3 Scenes of Oblivion being applied, the librarian with the status is turned into a pumpkin next Scene.
Afterwards, the real Jack transforms into 'Jack Revived', and permanently uses the Key page and Combat Pages of the librarian that had Oblivion.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704024">
<Name>เศษเสี้ยวจากทางใต้</Name>
<Desc>Gains 2 Strength every Scene</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704025">
<Name>เศษเสี้ยวจากทางตะวันตก</Name>
<Desc>Gains 2 Endurance every Scene</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704026">
<Name>เศษเสี้ยวจากทางเหนือ</Name>
<Desc>Gains 1 Haste every Scene</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704027">
<Name>เศษเสี้ยวจากทางตะวันออก</Name>
<Desc>Gains a buff that increases Stagger damage by 3 every Scene</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!--되살아난 잭-->
<PassiveDesc ID="704031">
<Name>ทั้งหมดเป็นของฉัน!!!</Name>
<Desc>Uses the Key page and Combat Pages of the librarian that has turned into a pumpkin.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="704032">
<Name>Perfect Jack</Name>
<Desc>Gain 2 Strength, 2 Endurance, 1 Haste, and a buff that increases Stagger damage by 3 every Scene</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<!--기억을 잃은 호박-->
<PassiveDesc ID="704041">
<Name>เสียความทรงจำ</Name>
<Desc>All Combat Pages change to unique ones. All stats change. Other passive abilities of this character will not activate.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!--푸른별의 제단-->
<PassiveDesc ID="903011">
<Name>Sacred?</Name>
<Desc>Cannot be targeted. Immune to status ailments.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="903012">
<Name>เสียงของดวงดาว</Name>
<Desc>Starting with the third Scene, the Shrine to the Blue Star uses a Mass Attack page every 3 Scenes.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="903013">
<Name>Into the Star’s Embrace</Name>
<Desc>If a character is Staggered, kill them and lose 10% of Max HP.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="903014">
<Name>The Blue Gleam of Hope</Name>
<Desc>If a &lt;Worshipper&gt; dies from the effect of 'Into the Star’s Embrace', all librarians recover Stagger Resist, and all Worshippers take Stagger damage.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="903015">
<Name>The Blue Glimmer of Despair</Name>
<Desc>If a &lt;librarian&gt; dies from the effect of 'Into the Star’s Embrace', all Worshippers recover Stagger Resist, and all librarians take Stagger damage.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!--푸른별의 신도-->
<PassiveDesc ID="903021">
<Name>ฉันได้ยินมัน!! เสียงของดวงดาวน่ะ!!</Name>
<Desc>Uses a special Combat Page on the Scene when the Shrine to the Blue Star uses a Mass Attack page. If the character's Stagger Resist is 40% or lower, instead uses a page that causes the character to self-destruct.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="903022">
<Name>Martyrs</Name>
<Desc>If there are less than 4 Worshippers present เมื่อเริ่มฉาก, a Worshipper is spawned.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
</PassiveDescRoot>