<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<PassiveDesc ID="1303011">
<Name>ประกายแสง</Name>
<Desc>เมื่อเริ่มต้นในแต่ละฉาก สลาย Page ทั้งหมดในมือและในกอง
เพิ่ม Page ชุดดังกล่าวกลับเข้ามาใหม่ และมีคอส 0</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1303012">
<Name>สดใหม่ และพร้อม</Name>
<Desc>HP does not go below 30%. If HP drops to 40% or lower, proceeds to the next phase.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<!--2페이즈에 나옴-->
<PassiveDesc ID="1303013">
<Name>งานเลี้้ยงมื้อใหญ่</Name>
<Desc>When the phase begins, defeat all Fresh Meats and recover HP based on the amount the Meats had. Also, gain 1 Strength.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="1303014">
<Name>เซลล์เนื้อฟื้นฟูตนเอง</Name>
<Desc>At the start of the act, gain 20 Resilience. Every 5 Scenes, purge all status ailments on self and gain 10 Resilience.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
 <PassiveDesc ID="1303015">
<Name>หนังฉลาม</Name>
<Desc>Gain 3 Protection each Scene. Take +3 additional damage from attacks while afflicted with Bleed.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>
<PassiveDesc ID="1303016">
<Name>หิวกระหายไม่หยุดยั้ง</Name>
<Desc>Cannot be Staggered. When Stagger Resist falls to 0, loses 100 HP instead and gains 1 Strength next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

 <!--뒤틀림-->
<PassiveDesc ID="1403011">
<Name>อัศวินฟันเจิดจ้า</Name>
<Desc>While alive, all other allies gain 1 Protection and Stagger Protection.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="1403012">
<Name>กาดด์ เพอร์ดูว์</Name> <!-- Get it? Like Pain Perdu :) -->
<Desc>Upon death, all allies are inflicted with 5 Fragile next Scene.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="1403013">
<Name>หยอดเกลือที่แผลสด</Name>
<Desc>If the target has 5 or more Bleed, the first die this character plays in the engagement inflicts 1 Fragile on hit.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

<PassiveDesc ID="1403014">
<Name>หนังกำพร้าฟื้นสภาพ</Name>
<Desc>If the character was not hit by any attacks for a Scene, recover 10 HP and gain 1 Strength.</Desc>
</PassiveDesc>

</PassiveDescRoot>
