<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Liu</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Liu-Fixer">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">ตาจะมองตรงไปข้างหน้า เมื่อต้องก้าวต่อไป</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">ฉันจะไม่หันหลังให้ศัตรูเด็ดขาด</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">เพื่อเป็นมังกรในสนามรบ ก็ควรจะเป็นคนที่มีเกียรติและกล้าหาญ…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">ไม่ว่านายจะทำอะไร ก็ไม่สามารถกระทบร่างกายและจิตใจฉันได้</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_4">นี้อาจจะไม่ใช่งานปกติที่เราทำ แต่แน่นอนว่าเราก็สามารถจัดการได้ด้วยเหมื่อนกัน</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_5">อย่าลืมมาตรการเดิมละ… นั้นคือการอย่าประมาท</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_6">แค่นี้ผมไม่กลัวหรอก ก็แค่บุกเข้าไป!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_7">สมาพันธ์หลิว นั้นไร้เทียมทาน</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_8">เราต้องรีบรุกขึ้นหน้า</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_9">หน้าที่ของคนๆหนึ่ง ก็คืออย่าขัดขวางทุกๆคน</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">ไม่อยากเชื่อเลยว่าพวกมือสมัครเล่นจะมาได้ถึงระดับนี้…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">ในที่สุดเราก็ทำภารกิจนี้เร็จแล้ว… กลับกันเถอะ</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_2">ไม่ใช่ความคิดที่ดีนัก ในการจะมั่นใจในชัยชนะครั้งนี้มากจนเกินไป</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_3">ฉันจะไม่อ่อนข้อให้กับคู่ศัตรู</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_4">มันเป็นชัยชนะที่ราบรื่น งั้นมารับหนังสือที่ขอไว้และกลับกันเถอะ</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">ฉันเกลียดที่จะเป็นตัวถ่วงคนอื่น…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">ฉันไม่ต้องการยอมแพ้…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_2">การพลาดแบบนี้… มันเป็นความผิดพลาดเพียงอย่างเดียว……</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_3">การลังเลมันจะเป็นเพียงสิ่งที่ขัดขวางผู้อื่นเท่านั้น……</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_4">ดูเหมือนว่า… ฉันจะถึงขีดจำกัดแล้ว</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">เราจะไม่จมอยู่กับความรู้สึกส่วนตัว</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">…สิ่งที่เราทำได้ก็คือก้าวต่อไป โดยไม่พูดอะไร</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">มันเป็นเรื่องยากในการจะสงบสติอารมณ์ต่อความตายของใครบางคน</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">…พวกเรายังต้องดำเนินต่อไป</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">เราไม่สามารถหันหลังกลับได้ แม้ว่าตอนนี้จะเริ่มอันตรายก็ตาม</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">ผมหวังว่าการต่อสู้ครั้งต่อไปจะแก้ไขปัญหาได้เหมือนตอนนี้</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">การเชิญชวนผู้คนให้มาต่อสู้โดยไม่ประเมินความสามารถ นั้นจะเป็นความผิดพลาดของพวกคุณ</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">ฉันจะไม่ยอมปล่อยให้แม้แต่วินาทีเดียวให้ผ่านไปโดยเปล่าประโยชน์ ฉันจะไม่ปล่อยให้ศัตรูรอดพ้นสายตาของฉันไปได้</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_3">ในช่วงเวลาแบบนี้ อาวุธของตัวเองมันเป็นสิ่งเดียวที่วางใจได้</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_4">การโจมตีที่อ่อนแอแบบนี้จะไม่สามารถทำไรได้หรอก</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Lowell">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Focus. They aren’t pushovers by any means.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Cecil, Mei. Are you ready?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">As long as our body and mind are sound, the results won’t betray us.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">Don’t be scared. Remember that the key to the enemy’s defeat is within yourselves.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I understand that you’re tired, but don’t forget to take the books.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Victory was already in our hands when we entered, so it was inevitable that the enemy lost.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">…At least, I could do something for my own sake till the end.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">I’m sorry… Thank you for your efforts.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Your will shall carry on… I swear to win this battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">…Should we pull back? No, the situation isn’t right yet…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">In difficult situations, be on the defensive.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">Even if everyone else dies, as long as one person stands… There’s still a chance to win.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">The battle isn’t over yet. Stay focused!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">We’re pressing on further. This isn’t over just yet…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Even the most rigorously trained soldier has weaknesses in body and mind.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Cecil">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Yessir! Going forth right away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">We shall not let them attack us from our back. We’ll push forward with a steadfast spirit.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">We will advance before the enemy can assume a formation!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I think the intel we got here will prove to be handy.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">I wonder if Section 1 has finished their work by now. Shall we head back?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Perhaps I wasn’t fit… to best a Star of the City.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Now is the time for action! Don’t be discouraged!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">We can endure this. We won’t lose…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">With the right mindset… We can overcome situations like this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">We will retaliate with even greater strength!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">A clean finish.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">They’re almost finished… We’ll charge further into their ranks!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">I’m not exhausted in the slightest; I feel like I’m on fire!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Mei">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">I’m prepared! Moving out now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">There aren’t too many foes!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Know your enemy and know yourself! Then you won’t falter after a hundred fights.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I was just starting to get warmed up… That’s a bit of a shame!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">That was an easy formation to break!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Sorry, director… I could’ve toughed it out…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">I won’t stop here! Giving up would be a rude thing to do to all my colleagues that have passed away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">The battle is ongoing… It’s not finished yet!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Can’t let them have it their way… HERE I COME!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">I’m not foolish enough to let such a casualty surprise me.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Things seem to be on a smooth track!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Is everyone alright? We should know when to advance and when to hold our position.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">It’s too late to hope for victory when the battle has already begun!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>